{
  "uniqueId": "JLPT N1",
  "name": "JLPT N1 Reading Quiz",
  "article": "a",
  "instructions": "Type the reading of the below word in Hiragana!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "IMAGE",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "JISHO_QUESTION_WORD",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "NONE",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "QUESTION_AND_ANSWER_LINK_QUESTION",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "CONVERT_KANA",
  "compileImages": true,
  "commentFieldName": "Meaning",
  "cards": [
    {"question":"黙る","answer":["だまる"],"meaning":"to be silent"},
    {"meaning":"relation(ship)","question":"間柄","answer":["あいだがら"]},
    {"meaning":"likes and dislikes","question":"愛憎","answer":["あいぞう","あいにく"]},
    {"meaning":"to look up (to), to respect, to depend on, to ask for, to seek, to revere, to drink, to take","question":"仰ぐ","answer":["あおぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"suborder, subfamily","question":"亜科","answer":["あか"]},
    {"question":"籠","answer":["かご"],"meaning":"basket (shopping, etc.); hamper; cage"},
    {"meaning":"proof, evidence","question":"証","answer":["あかし"]},
    {"question":"麓","answer":["ふもと"],"meaning":"foot (of a mountain or hill); bottom; base"},
    {"meaning":"yearning, longing, aspiration","question":"憧れ","answer":["あこがれ"]},
    {"meaning":"flax, linen, hemp","question":"麻","answer":["あさ"]},
    {"meaning":"wretched, miserable, shameful, mean, despicable, abject","question":"浅ましい","answer":["あさましい"]},
    {"meaning":"to deceive","question":"欺く","answer":["あざむく"]},
    {"meaning":"vivid, clear, brilliant","question":"鮮やか","answer":["あざやか"]},
    {"meaning":"to be in a hurry, to be impatient","question":"焦る","answer":["あせる"]},
    {"meaning":"pressure, coercion, oppression","question":"圧迫","answer":["あっぱく"]},
    {"meaning":"treatment, service","question":"扱い","answer":["あつかい"]},
    {"meaning":"stress, pressure","question":"圧力","answer":["あつりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"heir, successor","question":"跡継ぎ","answer":["あとつぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"oil painting","question":"油絵","answer":["あぶらえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to behave like a spoiled child, to fawn on","question":"甘える","answer":["あまえる"]},
    {"meaning":"sweet flavour, mildness, flattery, stupidity","question":"甘口","answer":["あまくち"]},
    {"meaning":"net, network","question":"網","answer":["あみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to manipulate, to operate, to pull strings","question":"操る","answer":["あやつる"]},
    {"meaning":"to lay waste, to devastate, to damage, to invade, to break into","question":"荒らす","answer":["あらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be renewed","question":"改まる","answer":["あらたまる"]},
    {"meaning":"rough, rude","question":"荒っぽい","answer":["あらっぽい"]},
    {"meaning":"mental arithmetic","question":"暗算","answer":["あんざん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be anxious, to ponder","question":"案じる","answer":["あんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"sure enough, as usual","question":"案の定","answer":["あんのじょう"]},
    {"question":"鳥居","answer":["とりい"],"meaning":"torii; Shinto shrine archway"},
    {"question":"鬱陶しい","answer":["うっとうしい"],"meaning":"gloomy (e.g. mood); depressing, irritating; troublesome, heavy (weather); cloudy"},
    {"meaning":"excuse, explanation","question":"言い訳","answer":["いいわけ"]},
    {"meaning":"chic, style, purity, essence","question":"粋","answer":["いき","すい"]},
    {"meaning":"outside the area","question":"域外","answer":["いきがい"]},
    {"meaning":"1. details, whole story, sequence of events, particulars, how it started, how things got this way, 2. c","question":"経緯","answer":["いきさつ","けいい"]},
    {"meaning":"objection, dissent, protest","question":"異議","answer":["いぎ"]},
    {"question":"馬力","answer":["ばりき"],"meaning":"horsepower; hp, energy; vitality; vigour"},
    {"meaning":"different opinion, objection","question":"異見","answer":["いけん"]},
    {"meaning":"switching over to","question":"移行","answer":["いこう"]},
    {"meaning":"stone monument bearing an inscription","question":"碑","answer":["いしぶみ"]},
    {"meaning":"clothing, costume, outfit, garment, dress","question":"衣装","answer":["いしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"migration, immigration","question":"移住","answer":["いじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"the opposite sex","question":"異性","answer":["いせい"]},
    {"meaning":"historic ruins (remains relics)","question":"遺跡","answer":["いせき"]},
    {"meaning":"still, as yet","question":"依然","answer":["いぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"dependence, dependent, reliance","question":"依存","answer":["いそん","いぞん"]},
    {"meaning":"consign (goods (for sale) to a firm), entrust (person with something), commit","question":"委託","answer":["いたく"]},
    {"meaning":"tease, prank, trick, practical joke, mischief","question":"悪戯","answer":["いたずら"]},
    {"meaning":"very much, exceedingly, extremely","question":"至って","answer":["いたって"]},
    {"meaning":"unconditionally, as a rule","question":"一概に","answer":["いちがいに"]},
    {"meaning":"remarkable, considerable","question":"著しい","answer":["いちじるしい"]},
    {"meaning":"evenness, uniformity, monotony, equality","question":"一律","answer":["いちりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"all together, batch, one lump, one bundle, summing up","question":"一括","answer":["いっかつ"]},
    {"meaning":"at a stroke, with a single swoop","question":"一挙に","answer":["いっきょに"]},
    {"meaning":"a region, a zone, the whole place","question":"一帯","answer":["いったい"]},
    {"meaning":"to carry on (e.g. in ceremony), to run a business","question":"営む","answer":["いとなむ"]},
    {"meaning":"a change","question":"異動","answer":["いどう"]},
    {"meaning":"to challenge, to contend for, to make love to","question":"挑む","answer":["いどむ"]},
    {"meaning":"(flash of) lightning","question":"稲光","answer":["いなびかり"]},
    {"meaning":"prayer, supplication","question":"祈り","answer":["いのり"]},
    {"meaning":"emigration, immigration, emigrant, immigrant","question":"移民","answer":["いみん"]},
    {"meaning":"greedy, vulgar, shabby, humble, base, mean, vile","question":"卑しい","answer":["いやしい"]},
    {"meaning":"clothing","question":"衣料","answer":["いりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"power, might, authority, influence","question":"威力","answer":["いりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"clothes, clothing, garments","question":"衣類","answer":["いるい"]},
    {"meaning":"different opinion, objection","question":"異論","answer":["いろん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) mark, (2) symbol, (3) evidence","question":"印","answer":["しるし","いん"]},
    {"meaning":"stamp, seal","question":"印鑑","answer":["いんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"gloom, melancholy","question":"陰気","answer":["いんき"]},
    {"meaning":"retirement, retired person","question":"隠居","answer":["いんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to inherit, to succeed, to take over","question":"受け継ぐ","answer":["うけつぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"tide","question":"潮","answer":["うしお","しお"]},
    {"meaning":"swirl","question":"渦","answer":["うず"]},
    {"meaning":"to be buried, to be surrounded, to overflow, to be filled","question":"埋まる","answer":["うずまる","うまる"]},
    {"meaning":"the items, breakdown, classification","question":"内訳","answer":["うちわけ"]},
    {"meaning":"lawsuit, complaint","question":"訴え","answer":["うったえ"]},
    {"meaning":"bowl, vessel, container","question":"器","answer":["うつわ"]},
    {"meaning":"ability, skill, facility","question":"腕前","answer":["うでまえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to urge, to press, to suggest, to demand, to stimulate, to quicken, to incite, to invite (attention to)","question":"促す","answer":["うながす"]},
    {"meaning":"to bury","question":"埋め込む","answer":["うめこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"dried plum","question":"梅干し","answer":["うめぼし"]},
    {"meaning":"inside out, upside down","question":"裏返し","answer":["うらがえし"]},
    {"meaning":"to be moist, to be damp, to get wet, to profit by, to be watered, to receive benefits, to favor, to charm, t","question":"潤う","answer":["うるおう"]},
    {"meaning":"to be planted","question":"植わる","answer":["うわる"]},
    {"meaning":"management, administration, operation","question":"運営","answer":["うんえい"]},
    {"meaning":"freight rates, shipping expenses, fare","question":"運賃","answer":["うんちん"]},
    {"meaning":"transport, carriage","question":"運搬","answer":["うんぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"transportation","question":"運輸","answer":["うんゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"health, hygiene, sanitation, medical","question":"衛生","answer":["えいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"reflection, image","question":"映像","answer":["えいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"hero, great man","question":"英雄","answer":["えいゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"liquid, fluid","question":"液","answer":["えき"]},
    {"meaning":"inspection, reading","question":"閲覧","answer":["えつらん"]},
    {"meaning":"game, spoils, trophy","question":"獲物","answer":["えもの"]},
    {"meaning":"neck, collar, lapel, neckband","question":"襟","answer":["えり"]},
    {"meaning":"charming, fascinating, voluptuous","question":"艶","answer":["えん","つや","あで"]},
    {"meaning":"harmony, smoothness","question":"円滑","answer":["えんかつ"]},
    {"meaning":"veranda, porch, balcony, open corridor","question":"縁側","answer":["えんがわ"]},
    {"meaning":"coast, shore","question":"沿岸","answer":["えんがん"]},
    {"meaning":"along railway line","question":"沿線","answer":["えんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"marriage proposal, engagement","question":"縁談","answer":["えんだん"]},
    {"meaning":"tail, ridge","question":"尾","answer":["お"]},
    {"meaning":"emergency","question":"応急","answer":["おうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"gold","question":"黄金","answer":["おうごん"]},
    {"meaning":"subscription, application","question":"応募","answer":["おうぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"large build, large pattern","question":"大柄","answer":["おおがら"]},
    {"meaning":"outline, summary","question":"大筋","answer":["おおすじ"]},
    {"meaning":"full width, large scale, drastic","question":"大幅","answer":["おおはば"]},
    {"meaning":"to invade, to raid, to trespass, to violate, to intrude on","question":"侵す","answer":["おかす"]},
    {"meaning":"austere, majestic, dignified, stately, awful, impressive","question":"厳か","answer":["おごそか"]},
    {"meaning":"to be obtained, to end, to settle into, to fit into, to be settled, to be paid, to be delivered","question":"納まる","answer":["おさまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be frugal, to value, to regret","question":"惜しむ","answer":["おしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"male (animal)","question":"雄","answer":["おす"]},
    {"meaning":"to attack","question":"襲う","answer":["おそう"]},
    {"meaning":"to say, to speak, to tell, to talk","question":"仰っしゃる","answer":["おっしゃる"]},
    {"meaning":"1. strange, quaint, stylish, chic, spicy, queer, witty, tasty, romantic, 2. 2nd in rank, second sign of the","question":"乙","answer":["おつ","きのと"]},
    {"meaning":"to become weak, to decline, to wear, to abate, to decay, to wither, to waste away","question":"衰える","answer":["おとろえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to threaten, to coerce","question":"脅かす","answer":["おどかす","おびやかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to threaten, to menace","question":"脅す","answer":["おどす"]},
    {"meaning":"surprise, astonishment, wonder","question":"驚き","answer":["おどろき"]},
    {"meaning":"to wear, to carry, to be entrusted, to have, to take on, to have a trace of, to be tinged with","question":"帯びる","answer":["おびる"]},
    {"question":"頂","answer":["いただき"],"meaning":"crown (of head); summit (of mountain); spire, easy win for one, something received"},
    {"question":"面目","answer":["めんぼく"],"meaning":"face; honour; honor; reputation; prestige; dignity; credit, appearance; look"},
    {"meaning":"meaning, tenor, gist, effect, appearance, taste, grace, charm, refinement","question":"趣","answer":["おもむき"]},
    {"meaning":"to go, to proceed, to repair to, to become","question":"赴く","answer":["おもむく"]},
    {"meaning":"and, as well as","question":"及び","answer":["および"]},
    {"meaning":"to reach, to come up to, to amount to, to befall, to happen to, to extend, to match, to equal","question":"及ぶ","answer":["およぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"weave, weaving, woven item","question":"織","answer":["おり"]},
    {"meaning":"textile, fabric","question":"織物","answer":["おりもの"]},
    {"meaning":"to weave","question":"織る","answer":["おる"]},
    {"meaning":"foolish, stupid","question":"愚か","answer":["おろか"]},
    {"meaning":"gentle, mild, moderate","question":"温和","answer":["おんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"tentative, provisional","question":"仮","answer":["かり"]},
    {"meaning":"article counter","question":"個","answer":["か","こ"]},
    {"meaning":"-floor (counter), stories","question":"階","answer":["かい"]},
    {"meaning":"deterioration, changing for the worse","question":"改悪","answer":["かいあく"]},
    {"meaning":"reform, reformation, innovation","question":"改革","answer":["かいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"shell","question":"貝殻","answer":["かいがら"]},
    {"meaning":"class, rank, grade","question":"階級","answer":["かいきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"channel","question":"海峡","answer":["かいきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing","question":"介護","answer":["かいご"]},
    {"meaning":"holding a meeting, open an exhibition","question":"開催","answer":["かいさい"]},
    {"meaning":"repair, improvement","question":"改修","answer":["かいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"monster","question":"怪獣","answer":["かいじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"class, level, stratum, hierarchy","question":"階層","answer":["かいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"reclamation (of wasteland), cultivation, pioneer","question":"開拓","answer":["かいたく"]},
    {"meaning":"reform","question":"改定","answer":["かいてい"]},
    {"meaning":"revision","question":"改訂","answer":["かいてい"]},
    {"meaning":"highway","question":"街道","answer":["かいどう"]},
    {"meaning":"intervention","question":"介入","answer":["かいにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing, looking after","question":"介抱","answer":["かいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"dissection, autopsy","question":"解剖","answer":["かいぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"circulation","question":"回覧","answer":["かいらん"]},
    {"meaning":"improvement, reform","question":"改良","answer":["かいりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to look back, to turn around, to review","question":"顧みる","answer":["かえりみる"]},
    {"meaning":"to reflect","question":"省みる","answer":["かえりみる"]},
    {"meaning":"to publish, to print, to carry (an article), to put up, to hang out, to hoist, to fly (a sail), to float (a","question":"掲げる","answer":["かかげる"]},
    {"meaning":"extracurricular","question":"課外","answer":["かがい"]},
    {"meaning":"nucleus, kernel","question":"核","answer":["かく","さね"]},
    {"meaning":"beautiful passage of literature","question":"佳句","answer":["かく"]},
    {"meaning":"scattering, diffusion","question":"拡散","answer":["かくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"every kind, all sorts","question":"各種","answer":["かくしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"every other week","question":"隔週","answer":["かくしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"reform, innovation","question":"革新","answer":["かくしん"]},
    {"meaning":"acquisition, possession","question":"獲得","answer":["かくとく"]},
    {"meaning":"guarantee, ensure, maintain, insure, secure","question":"確保","answer":["かくほ"]},
    {"meaning":"revolution","question":"革命","answer":["かくめい"]},
    {"meaning":"running fast, double time","question":"駆け足","answer":["かけあし"]},
    {"meaning":"(foot) race","question":"駆けっこ","answer":["かけっこ"]},
    {"meaning":"to run (race esp. horse), to gallop, to canter","question":"駆ける","answer":["かける"]},
    {"question":"雨天","answer":["うてん"],"meaning":"rainy weather"},
    {"question":"雨具","answer":["あまぐ"],"meaning":"rain gear"},
    {"meaning":"passage, place, point, part","question":"箇所","answer":["かしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"burn, scald","question":"火傷","answer":["かしょう","やけど"]},
    {"meaning":"itemized form, itemization","question":"箇条書き","answer":["かじょうがき"]},
    {"meaning":"faint, dim, weak, indistinct, hazy, poor, wretched","question":"微か","answer":["かすか"]},
    {"meaning":"to grow hazy, to be misty","question":"霞む","answer":["かすむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to touch lightly, to take a percentage (from)","question":"擦る","answer":["かする","こする","する","なする","なぞる","さする"]},
    {"meaning":"Mars (planet)","question":"火星","answer":["かせい"]},
    {"meaning":"rivers","question":"河川","answer":["かせん"]},
    {"meaning":"synthetic fibres","question":"化繊","answer":["かせん"]},
    {"meaning":"depopulation","question":"過疎","answer":["かそ"]},
    {"meaning":"unrequited love","question":"片思い","answer":["かたおもい"]},
    {"meaning":"a smattering, talk like a baby, speak haltingly","question":"片言","answer":["かたこと","へんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"tidying up, finishing","question":"片付け","answer":["かたづけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to incline toward, to slant, to lurch","question":"傾く","answer":["かたむく","かたぶく"]},
    {"meaning":"to incline, to list, to bend, to lean, to tip, to tilt, to slant, to concentrate on, to ruin (a country), to","question":"傾ける","answer":["かたむける"]},
    {"meaning":"to harden, to freeze, to fortify","question":"固める","answer":["かためる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be one-sided, to incline, to be partial, to be prejudiced, to lean, to be biased","question":"偏る","answer":["かたよる"]},
    {"meaning":"beside(s), while, nearby","question":"傍ら","answer":["かたわら"]},
    {"meaning":"subject, theme, task","question":"課題","answer":["かだい"]},
    {"meaning":"flower bed","question":"花壇","answer":["かだん"]},
    {"meaning":"domestic animals, livestock, cattle","question":"家畜","answer":["かちく"]},
    {"meaning":"to come true (wish)","question":"叶う","answer":["かなう"]},
    {"question":"雑木","answer":["ぞうき","ざつぼく","ぞうぼく"],"meaning":"various kinds of small trees; assorted trees"},
    {"meaning":"iron rod, crowbar, horizontal bar (gymnastics)","question":"鉄棒","answer":["かなぼう","てつぼう"]},
    {"question":"関与","answer":["かんよ"],"meaning":"participation; taking part in; participating in; being concerned in"},
    {"meaning":"simultaneously","question":"兼ねて","answer":["かねて"]},
    {"meaning":"pomp, splendor, gaudiness","question":"華美","answer":["かび"]},
    {"meaning":"pollen","question":"花粉","answer":["かふん"]},
    {"meaning":"stock (company)","question":"株式","answer":["かぶしき"]},
    {"meaning":"money, currency, coinage","question":"貨幣","answer":["かへい"]},
    {"meaning":"crowded","question":"過密","answer":["かみつ"]},
    {"meaning":"bottle","question":"瓶","answer":["びん","かめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to entangle, to entwine","question":"絡む","answer":["からむ"]},
    {"meaning":"lower official","question":"下吏","answer":["かり"]},
    {"meaning":"barely, narrowly, just manage to do st","question":"辛うじて","answer":["かろうじて"]},
    {"meaning":"pipe, tube","question":"管","answer":["くだ","かん"]},
    {"meaning":"(tree) trunk","question":"幹","answer":["かん","みき"]},
    {"meaning":"crown, diadem, first, best, peerless, cap, naming, designating, initiating on coming of age, top character ra","question":"冠","answer":["かん","かんむり"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity, easiness, quasi-","question":"簡易","answer":["かんい"]},
    {"meaning":"strong feelings, deep emotion","question":"感慨","answer":["かんがい"]},
    {"meaning":"brevity, conciseness, simplicity","question":"簡潔","answer":["かんけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"resolution, reduction, return to origins","question":"還元","answer":["かんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"publication, issue","question":"刊行","answer":["かんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"advice, counsel, remonstrance, recommendation","question":"勧告","answer":["かんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing, (army) nurse","question":"看護","answer":["かんご"]},
    {"meaning":"conversion, change, exchange","question":"換算","answer":["かんさん"]},
    {"meaning":"observation, guarding, inspection, surveillance","question":"監視","answer":["かんし"]},
    {"meaning":"spectators, onlookers, members of the audience","question":"観衆","answer":["かんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"interference, intervention","question":"干渉","answer":["かんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sense of touch, feeling, sensation","question":"感触","answer":["かんしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"essential, fundamental, crucial, vital, main","question":"肝心","answer":["かんじん"]},
    {"meaning":"cheer, shout of joy","question":"歓声","answer":["かんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"infection, contagion","question":"感染","answer":["かんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"main line, trunk line","question":"幹線","answer":["かんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"customs, duty, tariff","question":"関税","answer":["かんぜい"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity, plain","question":"簡素","answer":["かんそ"]},
    {"meaning":"management, (executive) staff, leaders","question":"幹部","answer":["かんぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"pardon, forgiveness, forbearance","question":"勘弁","answer":["かんべん"]},
    {"meaning":"invitation, solicitation, canvassing, inducement, persuasion, encouragement","question":"勧誘","answer":["かんゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"forbearance, tolerance, generosity","question":"寛容","answer":["かんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"viewing","question":"観覧","answer":["かんらん"]},
    {"meaning":"bureaucrat, bureaucracy","question":"官僚","answer":["かんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"60th birthday","question":"還暦","answer":["かんれき"]},
    {"meaning":"presence, dignity","question":"貫禄","answer":["かんろく"]},
    {"meaning":"relief, mitigation","question":"緩和","answer":["かんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"imported goods, foreign money","question":"外貨","answer":["がいか"]},
    {"meaning":"general statement, outline","question":"概説","answer":["がいせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"corresponding, answering to, coming under","question":"該当","answer":["がいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"in the street","question":"街頭","answer":["がいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"general idea, concept, notion","question":"概念","answer":["がいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"outline, summary, gist, in brief","question":"概略","answer":["がいりゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"arts and sciences, liberal arts","question":"学芸","answer":["がくげい"]},
    {"meaning":"university graduate","question":"学士","answer":["がくし"]},
    {"meaning":"score (music)","question":"楽譜","answer":["がくふ"]},
    {"meaning":"academic background","question":"学歴","answer":["がくれき"]},
    {"meaning":"artistry, good taste, elegance, grace","question":"雅致","answer":["がち"]},
    {"meaning":"chorus, singing in a chorus","question":"合唱","answer":["がっしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"agreement, concurrence, conforming to","question":"合致","answer":["がっち"]},
    {"meaning":"combination, union, amalgamation, consolidation, merger, coalition, fusion, annexation, affiliation, incorpor","question":"合併","answer":["がっぺい"]},
    {"meaning":"ophthalmology","question":"眼科","answer":["がんか"]},
    {"meaning":"eyeball","question":"眼球","answer":["がんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"stubbornness, obstinacy","question":"頑固","answer":["がんこ"]},
    {"meaning":"rock","question":"岩石","answer":["がんせき"]},
    {"meaning":"planning, project","question":"企画","answer":["きかく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dress up","question":"着飾る","answer":["きかざる"]},
    {"meaning":"organ (of body), instrument","question":"器官","answer":["きかん"]},
    {"meaning":"quarterly (e.g. magazine)","question":"季刊","answer":["きかん"]},
    {"meaning":"hesitance, diffidence, feeling constraint, fear of troubling someone, having scruples about doing someth","question":"気兼ね","answer":["きがね"]},
    {"meaning":"cheerful, buoyant, lighthearted","question":"気軽","answer":["きがる"]},
    {"meaning":"effect, virtue, efficacy, impression","question":"効き目","answer":["ききめ"]},
    {"meaning":"fund, foundation","question":"基金","answer":["ききん"]},
    {"meaning":"abstain from voting, renunciation of a right","question":"棄権","answer":["きけん"]},
    {"meaning":"comedy, funny show","question":"喜劇","answer":["きげき"]},
    {"meaning":"origin, beginning, rise","question":"起源","answer":["きげん"]},
    {"meaning":"marriage, married","question":"既婚","answer":["きこん"]},
    {"meaning":"mention, entry","question":"記載","answer":["きさい"]},
    {"meaning":"affectation, conceit, snobbery","question":"気障","answer":["きざ"]},
    {"meaning":"signs, omen, symptoms","question":"兆し","answer":["きざし"]},
    {"meaning":"signs, omen, symptoms","question":"兆","answer":["きざし"]},
    {"meaning":"weather, climate","question":"気象","answer":["きしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"describing, descriptor","question":"記述","answer":["きじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"odd number","question":"奇数","answer":["きすう"]},
    {"meaning":"to build, to pile up, to amass","question":"築く","answer":["きずく"]},
    {"meaning":"to be hurt, to be wounded, to get injured","question":"傷付く","answer":["きずつく"]},
    {"meaning":"steamship","question":"汽船","answer":["きせん"]},
    {"meaning":"donation, presentation","question":"寄贈","answer":["きそう","きぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"noble, aristocrat","question":"貴族","answer":["きぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"to forge, to drill, to temper, to train, to discipline","question":"鍛える","answer":["きたえる"]},
    {"meaning":"tea drinking, tea house","question":"喫茶","answer":["きっさ"]},
    {"meaning":"orbit, railroad track","question":"軌道","answer":["きどう"]},
    {"meaning":"1st in rank, first sign of the Chinese calendar, shell, instep, grade A (きのえ); carapace, shell (こう)","question":"甲","answer":["きのえ","こう"]},
    {"meaning":"model, standard, pattern, norm, criterion, example","question":"規範","answer":["きはん"]},
    {"meaning":"undulation","question":"起伏","answer":["きふく"]},
    {"meaning":"scale, scope, plan, structure","question":"規模","answer":["きぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"dramatization (e.g. film)","question":"脚色","answer":["きゃくしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"scenario","question":"脚本","answer":["きゃくほん"]},
    {"meaning":"relief, rescue, reinforcement","question":"救援","answer":["きゅうえん"]},
    {"meaning":"ultimate, final, eventual","question":"究極","answer":["きゅうきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"narrow, tight, stiff, rigid, uneasy, formal, constrained","question":"窮屈","answer":["きゅうくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(plant) bulb","question":"球根","answer":["きゅうこん"]},
    {"meaning":"relief, aid, rescue, salvation, help","question":"救済","answer":["きゅうさい"]},
    {"meaning":"old friend, old friendship","question":"旧知","answer":["きゅうち"]},
    {"meaning":"palace","question":"宮殿","answer":["きゅうでん"]},
    {"meaning":"poverty","question":"窮乏","answer":["きゅうぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"hill","question":"丘陵","answer":["きゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"wonder, miracle","question":"驚異","answer":["きょうい"]},
    {"meaning":"association, society, organization","question":"協会","answer":["きょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"conference, consultation, discussion, negotiation","question":"協議","answer":["きょうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"lesson, precept, moral instruction","question":"教訓","answer":["きょうくん"]},
    {"meaning":"environment, circumstances","question":"境遇","answer":["きょうぐう"]},
    {"meaning":"firm, vigorous, unbending, unyielding, strong, stubborn","question":"強硬","answer":["きょうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"bad harvest, poor crop","question":"凶作","answer":["きょうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"teaching materials","question":"教材","answer":["きょうざい"]},
    {"meaning":"nostalgia, homesickness","question":"郷愁","answer":["きょうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"reception, acceptance, enjoyment, being given","question":"享受","answer":["きょうじゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"to amuse oneself, to make merry","question":"興じる","answer":["きょうじる"]},
    {"meaning":"co-operation, conciliation, harmony, firm (market) tone","question":"協調","answer":["きょうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement, pact, agreement","question":"協定","answer":["きょうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"threat, menace, coercion, terrorism","question":"脅迫","answer":["きょうはく"]},
    {"meaning":"strong, intense, severe","question":"強烈","answer":["きょうれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"extreme, extremity","question":"極端","answer":["きょくたん"]},
    {"meaning":"refusal, rejection","question":"拒絶","answer":["きょぜつ"]},
    {"meaning":"denial, veto, rejection, refusal","question":"拒否","answer":["きょひ"]},
    {"meaning":"distance, range","question":"距離","answer":["きょり"]},
    {"meaning":"clean, pure, chaste","question":"清らか","answer":["きよらか"]},
    {"meaning":"paulownia tree","question":"桐","answer":["きり"]},
    {"meaning":"to change, to exchange, to convert, to renew, to throw a switch, to replace, to switch over","question":"切り替える","answer":["きりかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"pretty, clean, nice, tidy, beautiful, fair","question":"奇麗","answer":["きれい"]},
    {"meaning":"exceedingly, extremely","question":"極めて","answer":["きわめて"]},
    {"meaning":"nearsightedness, shortsightedness, myopia","question":"近眼","answer":["きんがん"]},
    {"meaning":"urgent, pressing, emergency","question":"緊急","answer":["きんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"suburbs, outskirts","question":"近郊","answer":["きんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"equilibrium, balance","question":"均衡","answer":["きんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"shortsightedness","question":"近視","answer":["きんし"]},
    {"meaning":"to prohibit","question":"禁じる","answer":["きんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to forbid, to suppress","question":"禁ずる","answer":["きんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"taboo, forbidden thing","question":"禁物","answer":["きんもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"legislative bill","question":"議案","answer":["ぎあん"]},
    {"meaning":"play, drama","question":"戯曲","answer":["ぎきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"sacrifice","question":"犠牲","answer":["ぎせい"]},
    {"meaning":"forgery, falsification, fabrication, counterfeiting","question":"偽造","answer":["ぎぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"technical skill, ability, capacity","question":"技能","answer":["ぎのう"]},
    {"meaning":"(sudden) change, reversal, turn-around, coming from behind (baseball)","question":"逆転","answer":["ぎゃくてん"]},
    {"meaning":"achievement, performance, results, work, contribution","question":"業績","answer":["ぎょうせき"]},
    {"question":"金銭","answer":["きんせん"],"meaning":"money; cash"},
    {"meaning":"fishing boat","question":"漁船","answer":["ぎょせん"]},
    {"meaning":"fishing village","question":"漁村","answer":["ぎょそん"]},
    {"meaning":"duty, sense of duty, honor, decency, courtesy, debt of gratitude, social obligation","question":"義理","answer":["ぎり"]},
    {"meaning":"doubt, misgivings, distrust, suspicion","question":"疑惑","answer":["ぎわく"]},
    {"meaning":"testing, scrutiny, careful investigation","question":"吟味","answer":["ぎんみ"]},
    {"meaning":"ward, district, section","question":"区","answer":["く"]},
    {"meaning":"division, section, compartment, boundary, area, block","question":"区画","answer":["くかく"]},
    {"meaning":"section (of track etc)","question":"区間","answer":["くかん"]},
    {"meaning":"stalk","question":"茎","answer":["くき"]},
    {"meaning":"an end, a stop, punctuation","question":"区切り","answer":["くぎり"]},
    {"meaning":"1. to drive, to pass through, 2. to evade, to hide, 3. to dive (into or under water), to go undergro","question":"潜る","answer":["くぐる","もぐる"]},
    {"meaning":"past events, bygones","question":"旧事","answer":["くじ","きゅうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to rot","question":"朽ちる","answer":["くちる"]},
    {"meaning":"bending, indentation, refraction","question":"屈折","answer":["くっせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to overturn, to upset, to overthrow, to undermine","question":"覆す","answer":["くつがえす"]},
    {"question":"金輪際","answer":["こんりんざい"],"meaning":"the deepest bottom of the earth; never; not ... at all; on no account; for all the world; till doomsday"},
    {"meaning":"necklace","question":"首飾り","answer":["くびかざり"]},
    {"meaning":"necklace, choker","question":"首輪","answer":["くびわ"]},
    {"meaning":"warehouse, cellar, magazine, granary, godown, depository, treasury, elevator","question":"蔵","answer":["くら"]},
    {"meaning":"expert, professional, geisha, prostitute","question":"玄人","answer":["くろうと"]},
    {"meaning":"idle complaint, grumble","question":"愚痴","answer":["ぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"group (math)","question":"群","answer":["ぐん"]},
    {"meaning":"warship, battleship","question":"軍艦","answer":["ぐんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"(social) group, crowd, throng, mob, multitude","question":"群集","answer":["ぐんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"military affairs","question":"軍事","answer":["ぐんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"armaments, military preparations","question":"軍備","answer":["ぐんび"]},
    {"meaning":"military or naval uniform","question":"軍服","answer":["ぐんぷく"]},
    {"meaning":"penalty, sentence, punishment","question":"刑","answer":["けい"]},
    {"meaning":"system, lineage, group","question":"系","answer":["けい"]},
    {"meaning":"rhythmical (e.g. melody), casual (e.g. dress), light, nimble","question":"軽快","answer":["けいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"warning, admonition, vigilance","question":"警戒","answer":["けいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"meter, gauge","question":"計器","answer":["けいき"]},
    {"meaning":"opportunity, chance","question":"契機","answer":["けいき"]},
    {"meaning":"Sincerely yours","question":"敬具","answer":["けいぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"abatement","question":"軽減","answer":["けいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"appearance (e.g. article in paper)","question":"掲載","answer":["けいさい"]},
    {"meaning":"inclination, slant, slope, bevel, list, dip","question":"傾斜","answer":["けいしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"condition, situation, prospects","question":"形勢","answer":["けいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"rash, thoughtless, careless, hasty","question":"軽率","answer":["けいそつ"]},
    {"meaning":"carrying something","question":"携帯","answer":["けいたい"]},
    {"meaning":"form, shape, figure","question":"形態","answer":["けいたい"]},
    {"meaning":"judgement, penalty, punishment","question":"刑罰","answer":["けいばつ"]},
    {"meaning":"personal history, career","question":"経歴","answer":["けいれき"]},
    {"question":"金融","answer":["きんゆう"],"meaning":"financing; credit transacting; loaning of money; circulation of money"},
    {"meaning":"filthy, unfair","question":"汚らわしい","answer":["けがらわしい"]},
    {"meaning":"uncleanness, impurity, disgrace","question":"汚れ","answer":["けがれ","よごれ"]},
    {"meaning":"beast, brute","question":"獣","answer":["けだもの","けもの"]},
    {"meaning":"tuberculosis, tubercule","question":"結核","answer":["けっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"blood vessel","question":"血管","answer":["けっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"balance sheet, settlement of accounts","question":"決算","answer":["けっさん"]},
    {"meaning":"crystal, crystallization","question":"結晶","answer":["けっしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"formation","question":"結成","answer":["けっせい"]},
    {"meaning":"union, unity","question":"結束","answer":["けっそく"]},
    {"meaning":"combination, union","question":"結合","answer":["けつごう"]},
    {"meaning":"want, shortage, famine","question":"欠乏","answer":["けつぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"sphere, circle, range","question":"圏","answer":["けん"]},
    {"meaning":"authority, power, influence","question":"権威","answer":["けんい"]},
    {"meaning":"side line, second business","question":"兼業","answer":["けんぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"in good health, well","question":"健在","answer":["けんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"offering prizes, winning, reward","question":"懸賞","answer":["けんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"public prosecutor","question":"検事","answer":["けんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"health, soundness, wholesome","question":"健全","answer":["けんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"wisdom, intelligence, prudence","question":"賢明","answer":["けんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"thrift, economy, frugality","question":"倹約","answer":["けんやく"]},
    {"meaning":"multi-use, combined use, combination, serving two purposes","question":"兼用","answer":["けんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"troupe, theatrical company","question":"劇団","answer":["げきだん"]},
    {"meaning":"encouragement","question":"激励","answer":["げきれい"]},
    {"meaning":"monthly tuition fee","question":"月謝","answer":["げっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"monthly installment","question":"月賦","answer":["げっぷ"]},
    {"meaning":"diarrhoea","question":"下痢","answer":["げり"]},
    {"meaning":"decrease, reduction, decline","question":"減少","answer":["げんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"chemical element","question":"元素","answer":["げんそ"]},
    {"meaning":"principle, general rule","question":"原則","answer":["げんそく"]},
    {"meaning":"developing (film)","question":"現像","answer":["げんぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"original (text)","question":"原典","answer":["げんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"subtract, give a demerit","question":"減点","answer":["げんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"atomic bomb","question":"原爆","answer":["げんばく"]},
    {"meaning":"strict, close","question":"厳密","answer":["げんみつ"]},
    {"meaning":"crude oil","question":"原油","answer":["げんゆ"]},
    {"question":"重なる","answer":["かさなる","おもなる"],"meaning":"to be piled up; to lie on top of one another, to come one after another; to happen over and over; to pile up (e.g. stress); to accumulate, to overlap (each other); to occur at the same time; to happen simultaneously, main; principal; important"},
    {"meaning":"to fall in love with, to love","question":"恋する","answer":["こいする"]},
    {"meaning":"10^38, hundred undecillion, hundred sextillion (こう), ditch, drain, gutter, trench (みぞ)","question":"溝","answer":["こう","みぞ","どぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"act, deed, conduct","question":"行為","answer":["こうい"]},
    {"meaning":"regret, repentance","question":"後悔","answer":["こうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"sail, voyage","question":"航海","answer":["こうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"Imperial Palace","question":"皇居","answer":["こうきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"prosperous conditions, healthy economy","question":"好況","answer":["こうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"protest, objection","question":"抗議","answer":["こうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"mining industry","question":"鉱業","answer":["こうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"industrial enterprise","question":"興業","answer":["こうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"cultivation, farming","question":"耕作","answer":["こうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"mine (ore)","question":"鉱山","answer":["こうざん"]},
    {"meaning":"short course, training","question":"講習","answer":["こうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"negotiations, discussions, connection","question":"交渉","answer":["こうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"high, noble, refined, advanced","question":"高尚","answer":["こうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"spices","question":"香辛料","answer":["こうしんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"verbal statement","question":"口述","answer":["こうじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"subsidy, deduction","question":"控除","answer":["こうじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"flood","question":"洪水","answer":["こうずい"]},
    {"meaning":"dispute, resistance","question":"抗争","answer":["こうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"restriction, restraint","question":"拘束","answer":["こうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"brilliance, polish, lustre, glossy finish (of photographs)","question":"光沢","answer":["こうたく"]},
    {"meaning":"public corporation","question":"公団","answer":["こうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"reading, translation","question":"講読","answer":["こうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"subscription (e.g. magazine)","question":"購読","answer":["こうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"purchase, buy","question":"購入","answer":["こうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"ruin","question":"荒廃","answer":["こうはい"]},
    {"meaning":"purchase, buy","question":"購買","answer":["こうばい"]},
    {"meaning":"popularity, favorable reputation","question":"好評","answer":["こうひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"capitulation, surrender, submission","question":"降伏","answer":["こうふく"]},
    {"meaning":"excitement, stimulation, agitation, arousal","question":"興奮","answer":["こうふん"]},
    {"meaning":"public appeal, public contribution","question":"公募","answer":["こうぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"ingenious, skillful, clever, deft","question":"巧妙","answer":["こうみょう"]},
    {"meaning":"efficiency","question":"効率","answer":["こうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"short (build)","question":"小柄","answer":["こがら"]},
    {"meaning":"national defence","question":"国防","answer":["こくぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"black tea","question":"焦げ茶","answer":["こげちゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"individual, one by one","question":"個々","answer":["ここ"]},
    {"question":"郷里","answer":["きょうり"],"meaning":"birth-place; home town"},
    {"meaning":"will, intention, motive","question":"志","answer":["こころざし"]},
    {"meaning":"to plan, to intend, to aspire to, to set aims (sights on)","question":"志す","answer":["こころざす"]},
    {"meaning":"helpless, forlorn, hopeless, unpromising, lonely, discouraging, disheartening","question":"心細い","answer":["こころぼそい"]},
    {"meaning":"pleasant, agreeable","question":"快い","answer":["こころよい"]},
    {"meaning":"to freeze, to congeal","question":"凝らす","answer":["こごらす","こらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to congeal, to freeze","question":"凝る","answer":["こごる","こる","しこる"]},
    {"meaning":"orphan","question":"孤児","answer":["こじ"]},
    {"meaning":"the deceased, old friend","question":"故人","answer":["こじん"]},
    {"meaning":"treetop","question":"梢","answer":["こずえ"]},
    {"meaning":"individuality, personality, idiosyncrasy","question":"個性","answer":["こせい"]},
    {"meaning":"census, family register","question":"戸籍","answer":["こせき"]},
    {"meaning":"coins, small change","question":"小銭","answer":["こぜに"]},
    {"meaning":"solid (body)","question":"固体","answer":["こたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear, to stand, to endure, to put up with, to support, to withstand, to resist, to brave, to be fit for, t","question":"堪える","answer":["こらえる","たえる","こたえる"]},
    {"meaning":"exaggeration","question":"誇張","answer":["こちょう"]},
    {"question":"道化","answer":["どうけ"],"meaning":"antics; buffoonery; clowning, clown; jester"},
    {"meaning":"fixation","question":"固定","answer":["こてい"]},
    {"meaning":"matter, thing, affair, circumstance","question":"事柄","answer":["ことがら"]},
    {"meaning":"especially, above all","question":"殊に","answer":["ことに"]},
    {"meaning":"isolation, loneliness, solitude","question":"孤独","answer":["こどく"]},
    {"meaning":"in very small pieces","question":"粉々","answer":["こなごな"]},
    {"meaning":"particular case","question":"個別","answer":["こべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to spill","question":"零す","answer":["こぼす"]},
    {"meaning":"to overflow, to spill","question":"零れる","answer":["こぼれる"]},
    {"meaning":"friendly","question":"細やか","answer":["こまやか","ささやか"]},
    {"meaning":"to be crowded","question":"混む","answer":["こむ"]},
    {"meaning":"characteristic, tradition, peculiar, inherent, eigen-","question":"固有","answer":["こゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"employment (long term), hire","question":"雇用","answer":["こよう"]},
    {"meaning":"calendar, almanac","question":"暦","answer":["こよみ"]},
    {"meaning":"isolation, helplessness","question":"孤立","answer":["こりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to learn by experience, to be disgusted with","question":"懲りる","answer":["こりる"]},
    {"meaning":"soul, spirit","question":"魂","answer":["こん","たましい"]},
    {"meaning":"patience, perseverance, energy","question":"根気","answer":["こんき"]},
    {"meaning":"basis, foundation","question":"根拠","answer":["こんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"mixed race, mixed parentage","question":"混血","answer":["こんけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"insect, bug","question":"昆虫","answer":["こんちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"root, basis, foundation","question":"根底","answer":["こんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"confusion, mixing, merger","question":"混同","answer":["こんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"origin, source, foundation, root, base, principle","question":"根本","answer":["こんぽん","ねもと"]},
    {"meaning":"guard, convoy, escort","question":"護衛","answer":["ごえい"]},
    {"meaning":"words, phrases","question":"語句","answer":["ごく"]},
    {"meaning":"paradise","question":"極楽","answer":["ごくらく"]},
    {"meaning":"word root, word derivation, etymology","question":"語源","answer":["ごげん"]},
    {"meaning":"Go board","question":"碁盤","answer":["ごばん"]},
    {"meaning":"to deceive, to falsify, to misrepresent","question":"誤魔化す","answer":["ごまかす"]},
    {"question":"遊山","answer":["ゆさん"],"meaning":"excursion; outing; picnic"},
    {"meaning":"(please) look, (please) try to do","question":"御覧なさい","answer":["ごらんなさい"]},
    {"question":"進捗","answer":["しんちょく"],"meaning":"progress; being under way"},
    {"question":"連ねる","answer":["つらねる"],"meaning":"to line up; to put in a row, to add (to a group); to accept (as a member of an organization, etc.); to join (e.g. a list), to link; to put together; to string together (e.g. compliments); to enumerate, to take along with; to bring with"},
    {"meaning":"difference, disparity","question":"差異","answer":["さい"]},
    {"meaning":"another meeting, meeting again, reunion","question":"再会","answer":["さいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"calamity, disaster, misfortune","question":"災害","answer":["さいがい"]},
    {"meaning":"bacillus, bacterium, germ","question":"細菌","answer":["さいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"work, craftsmanship, tactics, trick","question":"細工","answer":["さいく"]},
    {"meaning":"mining","question":"採掘","answer":["さいくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"vote, roll call","question":"採決","answer":["さいけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"rebuilding, reconstruction, rehabilitation","question":"再建","answer":["さいけん"]},
    {"meaning":"reappearance, reproduction, return, revival","question":"再現","answer":["さいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"profit","question":"採算","answer":["さいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"collecting, gathering","question":"採集","answer":["さいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"playback, regeneration, resuscitation, return to life, rebirth, reincarnation, narrow escape, reclamation, r","question":"再生","answer":["さいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"the very best","question":"最善","answer":["さいぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"adoption, selection, choice","question":"採択","answer":["さいたく"]},
    {"meaning":"return, relapse, reoccurrence","question":"再発","answer":["さいはつ"]},
    {"meaning":"cultivation","question":"栽培","answer":["さいばい"]},
    {"meaning":"cell (biology)","question":"細胞","answer":["さいぼう","さいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"use, adopt","question":"採用","answer":["さいよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to interrupt, to intercept, to obstruct","question":"遮る","answer":["さえぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be clear, to be serene, to be cold, to be skillful","question":"冴える","answer":["さえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to prosper, to flourish","question":"栄える","answer":["さかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"handstand, headstand","question":"逆立ち","answer":["さかだち"]},
    {"meaning":"to go back, to go upstream, to make retroactive","question":"逆上る","answer":["さかのぼる"]},
    {"question":"連なる","answer":["つらなる"],"meaning":"to extend; to stretch out; to stand in a row, to attend; to participate in, to enrol; to join, to have a connection; to be related; to be linked"},
    {"meaning":"balance, difference, margin","question":"差額","answer":["さがく"]},
    {"meaning":"fraud, swindle","question":"詐欺","answer":["さぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"plan, policy","question":"策","answer":["さく"]},
    {"meaning":"cut, reduction, curtailment","question":"削減","answer":["さくげん"]},
    {"meaning":"mistake","question":"錯誤","answer":["さくご"]},
    {"meaning":"shout, scream, outcry","question":"叫び","answer":["さけび"]},
    {"meaning":"to split, to tear, to burst","question":"裂ける","answer":["さける"]},
    {"meaning":"to grant, to award, to teach","question":"授ける","answer":["さずける"]},
    {"meaning":"optical illusion, hallucination","question":"錯覚","answer":["さっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for books","question":"冊","answer":["さつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to attain enlightenment, to perceive, to understand, to discern","question":"悟る","answer":["さとる"]},
    {"meaning":"to judge","question":"裁く","answer":["さばく"]},
    {"meaning":"three-stringed Japanese guitar, shamisen","question":"三味線","answer":["しゃみせん","さみせん"]},
    {"meaning":"Samurai, warrior","question":"侍","answer":["さむらい"]},
    {"meaning":"fresh, refreshing, invigorating, clear, fluent, eloquent","question":"爽やか","answer":["さわやか"]},
    {"meaning":"to hinder, to interfere with, to affect, to do one harm, to be harmful to","question":"障る","answer":["さわる"]},
    {"meaning":"acid","question":"酸","answer":["さん"]},
    {"meaning":"oxidation","question":"酸化","answer":["さんか"]},
    {"meaning":"mountains","question":"山岳","answer":["さんがく"]},
    {"meaning":"wharf, bridge, jetty, pier","question":"桟橋","answer":["さんきょう","さんばし"]},
    {"meaning":"reference, consultation, consultation","question":"参照","answer":["さんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"mountain range","question":"山脈","answer":["さんみゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"source of funds, resources, finances","question":"財源","answer":["ざいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"stockpile, stock","question":"在庫","answer":["ざいこ"]},
    {"meaning":"miscellaneous goods, general goods, sundries","question":"雑貨","answer":["ざっか"]},
    {"meaning":"coordinate(s)","question":"座標","answer":["ざひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"cruelty, harshness","question":"残酷","answer":["ざんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"breeding, raising, rearing","question":"飼育","answer":["しいく"]},
    {"meaning":"sense of sight, vision","question":"視覚","answer":["しかく"]},
    {"meaning":"urban areas, the streets, town, city","question":"市街","answer":["しがい"]},
    {"meaning":"command, direction","question":"指揮","answer":["しき"]},
    {"meaning":"colour, hue, tints","question":"色彩","answer":["しきさい"]},
    {"meaning":"frequently, repeatedly, incessantly, eagerly","question":"頻りに","answer":["しきりに"]},
    {"meaning":"1. execution, enforcing, carrying out","question":"施行","answer":["しぎょう","しこう","せこう"]},
    {"meaning":"death penalty, capital punishment","question":"死刑","answer":["しけい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be damp, to be moist","question":"湿気る","answer":["しける","しっける"]},
    {"meaning":"intention, aim","question":"志向","answer":["しこう"]},
    {"meaning":"inspection, observation","question":"視察","answer":["しさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to sink, to submerge","question":"沈める","answer":["しずめる"]},
    {"meaning":"institution, establishment, facility, (army) engineer","question":"施設","answer":["しせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to yearn for, to miss, to adore, to love dearly","question":"慕う","answer":["したう"]},
    {"meaning":"therefore, consequently, in accordance with","question":"従って","answer":["したがって"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity, modesty, frugality","question":"質素","answer":["しっそ"]},
    {"meaning":"pointing out, identification","question":"指摘","answer":["してき"]},
    {"meaning":"opinion, point of view, visual point","question":"視点","answer":["してん"]},
    {"question":"途絶える","answer":["とだえる"],"meaning":"to stop; to cease; to come to an end"},
    {"meaning":"lawn, sod, turf","question":"芝","answer":["しば"]},
    {"meaning":"little while","question":"暫く","answer":["しばらく"]},
    {"meaning":"1. tasteful (clothing), cool, an aura of refined masculinity, 2. astringent, sullen, bitter (taste), 3","question":"渋い","answer":["しぶい"]},
    {"meaning":"administration of justice","question":"司法","answer":["しほう"]},
    {"meaning":"fat, grease, blubber","question":"脂肪","answer":["しぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"wish, desire, ambition","question":"志望","answer":["しぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"to pierce, to permeate","question":"染みる","answer":["しみる"]},
    {"meaning":"closing, cut-off, end, deadline, Closed, No Entrance","question":"締め切り","answer":["しめきり"]},
    {"meaning":"refusal","question":"謝絶","answer":["しゃぜつ"]},
    {"meaning":"slope, slanting surface, bevel","question":"斜面","answer":["しゃめん"]},
    {"meaning":"field of vision, outlook","question":"視野","answer":["しや"]},
    {"meaning":"masses, great number, the people","question":"衆","answer":["しゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"circuit, lap, circumference, vicinity, Chou (dynasty)","question":"周","answer":["しゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"earnings, proceeds, returns","question":"収益","answer":["しゅうえき"]},
    {"meaning":"learning","question":"修学","answer":["しゅうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"cycle, period","question":"周期","answer":["しゅうき"]},
    {"meaning":"Lower House, House of Representatives","question":"衆議院","answer":["しゅうぎいん"]},
    {"meaning":"employment, starting work","question":"就業","answer":["しゅうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"pursuit of knowledge, studying, learning, training, ascetic practice, discipline","question":"修行","answer":["しゅぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"attack, charge, raid","question":"襲撃","answer":["しゅうげき"]},
    {"meaning":"Masters degree program","question":"修士","answer":["しゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"ornamentation, embellishment, decoration, adornment, polish up (writing), modification (gram)","question":"修飾","answer":["しゅうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"attachment, adhesion, tenacity","question":"執着","answer":["しゅうじゃく","しゅうちゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"completion (of a course)","question":"修了","answer":["しゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"security guard, doorkeeper","question":"守衛","answer":["しゅえい"]},
    {"meaning":"celebration, congratulations","question":"祝賀","answer":["しゅくが"]},
    {"meaning":"handicrafts","question":"手芸","answer":["しゅげい"]},
    {"meaning":"organization, sponsorship","question":"主催","answer":["しゅさい"]},
    {"meaning":"choice of subject, collecting data","question":"取材","answer":["しゅざい"]},
    {"meaning":"object, meaning","question":"趣旨","answer":["しゅし"]},
    {"meaning":"bleeding, haemorrhage","question":"出血","answer":["しゅっけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"main leadership","question":"主導","answer":["しゅどう"]},
    {"meaning":"head, brains","question":"首脳","answer":["しゅのう"]},
    {"meaning":"various, many, several","question":"諸","answer":["しょ","もろ"]},
    {"question":"逐一","answer":["ちくいち"],"meaning":"one by one; in detail; minutely"},
    {"meaning":"illness","question":"症","answer":["しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"shock, crash, impact, ballistic","question":"衝撃","answer":["しょうげき"]},
    {"meaning":"evidence, testimony","question":"証言","answer":["しょうげん"]},
    {"meaning":"evidence, proof","question":"証拠","answer":["しょうこ"]},
    {"meaning":"exhaustion, consumption","question":"消耗","answer":["しょうこう","しょうもう"]},
    {"meaning":"collation, comparison","question":"照合","answer":["しょうごう"]},
    {"meaning":"detail, particulars","question":"詳細","answer":["しょうさい"]},
    {"meaning":"promotion","question":"昇進","answer":["しょうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"to pretend, to take the name of, to feign, to purport","question":"称する","answer":["しょうする"]},
    {"meaning":"consent, acquiescence, agreement","question":"承諾","answer":["しょうだく"]},
    {"meaning":"symbol","question":"象徴","answer":["しょうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"pediatrics","question":"小児科","answer":["しょうにか"]},
    {"meaning":"witness","question":"証人","answer":["しょうにん"]},
    {"meaning":"illumination","question":"照明","answer":["しょうめい"]},
    {"meaning":"encouragement, promotion, message, address","question":"奨励","answer":["しょうれい"]},
    {"meaning":"colony","question":"植民地","answer":["しょくみんち"]},
    {"meaning":"Gentlemen!, Ladies!","question":"諸君","answer":["しょくん"]},
    {"meaning":"attached to, belong to","question":"所属","answer":["しょぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"first edition","question":"初版","answer":["しょはん"]},
    {"meaning":"punishment","question":"処罰","answer":["しょばつ"]},
    {"meaning":"book review","question":"書評","answer":["しょひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"masses, common people","question":"庶民","answer":["しょみん"]},
    {"meaning":"general affairs","question":"庶務","answer":["しょむ"]},
    {"meaning":"orders, instructions, directive","question":"指令","answer":["しれい"]},
    {"meaning":"rear, rear unit guard (しんがり), master, lord (どの)","question":"殿","answer":["しんがり","との"]},
    {"meaning":"deliberation","question":"審議","answer":["しんぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"rising, developing, emergent","question":"新興","answer":["しんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"promotion, encouragement","question":"振興","answer":["しんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"judging, inspection, examination, investigation","question":"審査","answer":["しんさ"]},
    {"meaning":"gentleman","question":"紳士","answer":["しんし"]},
    {"meaning":"pearl","question":"真珠","answer":["しんじゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"holiness, sacredness, dignity","question":"神聖","answer":["しんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"friendship","question":"親善","answer":["しんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"new building, new construction","question":"新築","answer":["しんちく"]},
    {"meaning":"presentation","question":"進呈","answer":["しんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"progress, development","question":"進展","answer":["しんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"temple, sacred place","question":"神殿","answer":["しんでん"]},
    {"meaning":"oscillation, vibration","question":"振動","answer":["しんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"mystery","question":"神秘","answer":["しんぴ"]},
    {"meaning":"patience, endurance","question":"辛抱","answer":["しんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"aggression, invasion, raid","question":"侵略","answer":["しんりゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"medical examination and treatment, diagnosis","question":"診療","answer":["しんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"self, the ego","question":"自我","answer":["じが"]},
    {"meaning":"magnetism","question":"磁気","answer":["じき"]},
    {"meaning":"porcelain, china","question":"磁器","answer":["じき"]},
    {"meaning":"axis, stem, shaft, axle","question":"軸","answer":["じく"]},
    {"meaning":"self, oneself","question":"自己","answer":["じこ"]},
    {"meaning":"matter, item, facts","question":"事項","answer":["じこう"]},
    {"meaning":"hell","question":"地獄","answer":["じごく"]},
    {"meaning":"self-respect, conceit","question":"自尊心","answer":["じそんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"practice, put into practice","question":"実践","answer":["じっせん"]},
    {"meaning":"truth, fact","question":"実態","answer":["じったい"]},
    {"meaning":"intransitive verb (no direct obj)","question":"自動詞","answer":["じどうし"]},
    {"meaning":"otolaryngology","question":"耳鼻科","answer":["じびか"]},
    {"meaning":"weakness, the weak, little less then","question":"弱","answer":["じゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"some, few, number of","question":"若干","answer":["じゃっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"gravel, ballast, pebbles","question":"砂利","answer":["じゃり"]},
    {"question":"近々","answer":["ちかぢか","きんきん"],"meaning":"soon; nearness; before long"},
    {"meaning":"employee, worker","question":"従業員","answer":["じゅうぎょういん"]},
    {"meaning":"engaging, pursuing, following","question":"従事","answer":["じゅうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"fullness, completion, perfection, substantiality, enrichment","question":"充実","answer":["じゅうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"flexible, lithe","question":"柔軟","answer":["じゅうなん"]},
    {"meaning":"duplication, repetition, overlapping, redundancy, restoration","question":"重複","answer":["じゅうふく","ちょうふく"]},
    {"meaning":"priceless treasure, convenience, usefulness","question":"重宝","answer":["じゅうほう","ちょうほう"]},
    {"meaning":"up to now, so far, traditional","question":"従来","answer":["じゅうらい"]},
    {"meaning":"coaching school, lessons","question":"塾","answer":["じゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"trees and shrubs, arbour","question":"樹木","answer":["じゅもく"]},
    {"meaning":"establish, create","question":"樹立","answer":["じゅりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"local express (train slower than an express)","question":"準急","answer":["じゅんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to follow, to conform, to apply to","question":"準じる","answer":["じゅんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to apply correspondingly, to correspond to, to be proportionate to, to conform to","question":"準ずる","answer":["じゅんずる"]},
    {"question":"辞退","answer":["じたい"],"meaning":"declining; refusal; nonacceptance; turning down; withdrawal (e.g. candidacy); pulling out (e.g. race); excusing oneself"},
    {"meaning":"young woman","question":"嬢","answer":["じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"land near the castle","question":"城下","answer":["じょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"superior authorities, boss","question":"上司","answer":["じょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"rising, ascending, climbing","question":"上昇","answer":["じょうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"state of things, condition, situation","question":"情勢","answer":["じょうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"concession, conciliation, compromise","question":"譲歩","answer":["じょうほ"]},
    {"meaning":"treaty, pact","question":"条約","answer":["じょうやく"]},
    {"meaning":"landing, disembarkation","question":"上陸","answer":["じょうりく"]},
    {"meaning":"distillation","question":"蒸留","answer":["じょうりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"going slowly","question":"徐行","answer":["じょこう"]},
    {"meaning":"Ms.","question":"女史","answer":["じょし"]},
    {"meaning":"particle, postposition","question":"助詞","answer":["じょし"]},
    {"meaning":"auxiliary verb","question":"助動詞","answer":["じょどうし"]},
    {"meaning":"man of talent","question":"人材","answer":["じんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"quick, fast, rapid, swift, prompt","question":"迅速","answer":["じんそく"]},
    {"meaning":"source of river, fountainhead","question":"水源","answer":["すいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"propulsion, driving force","question":"推進","answer":["すいしん"]},
    {"meaning":"playing wind instruments","question":"吹奏","answer":["すいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"guess, conjecture","question":"推測","answer":["すいそく"]},
    {"meaning":"reasoning, inference, mystery or detective genre (movie novel etc.)","question":"推理","answer":["すいり"]},
    {"meaning":"numeral","question":"数詞","answer":["すうし"]},
    {"meaning":"worship, adoration, admiration, cult","question":"崇拝","answer":["すうはい"]},
    {"meaning":"to install, to equip, to mount","question":"据え付ける","answer":["すえつける"]},
    {"meaning":"to set (table), to lay (foundation), to place (gun), to apply (moxa)","question":"据える","answer":["すえる"]},
    {"meaning":"help, aid, relief","question":"救い","answer":["すくい"]},
    {"meaning":"vigorous, healthy, sound","question":"健やか","answer":["すこやか"]},
    {"meaning":"recommendation, advice, encouragement","question":"勧め","answer":["すすめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to go out of use, to become obsolete, to die out, to go out of fashion","question":"廃れる","answer":["すたれる"]},
    {"meaning":"sour, acid","question":"酸っぱい","answer":["すっぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"lovely, dreamy, beautiful, great, fantastic, superb, cool, capital","question":"素敵","answer":["すてき"]},
    {"meaning":"fast, quick, prompt, agile","question":"素早い","answer":["すばやい"]},
    {"meaning":"to clear, to make clear, to be unruffled, to look unconcerned, to look demure, look prim, put on airs","question":"澄ます","answer":["すます"]},
    {"question":"軽蔑","answer":["けいべつ"],"meaning":"scorn; disdain; contempt"},
    {"meaning":"printing","question":"刷り","answer":["すり"]},
    {"meaning":"chance encounter","question":"擦れ違い","answer":["すれちがい"]},
    {"question":"身近","answer":["みぢか"],"meaning":"near oneself; close to one; familiar"},
    {"meaning":"-made, make","question":"製","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"justice, right, righteousness, correct meaning","question":"正義","answer":["せいぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"elaborate, delicate, exquisite","question":"精巧","answer":["せいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"restraint, sanctions, punishment","question":"制裁","answer":["せいさい"]},
    {"meaning":"political measures, policy","question":"政策","answer":["せいさく"]},
    {"meaning":"liquidation, settlement","question":"清算","answer":["せいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"constellation","question":"星座","answer":["せいざ"]},
    {"meaning":"Bible, scriptures","question":"聖書","answer":["せいしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"sincere, honest, faithful","question":"誠実","answer":["せいじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"maturity, ripeness","question":"成熟","answer":["せいじゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"purity, innocence","question":"清純","answer":["せいじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"orderly, regular, well-organized, trim, accurate","question":"整然","answer":["せいぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"be dressed up, wear rich clothes","question":"盛装","answer":["せいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"grand, prosperous, magnificent","question":"盛大","answer":["せいだい"]},
    {"meaning":"good and evil, purity and impurity","question":"清濁","answer":["せいだく"]},
    {"meaning":"iron manufacture","question":"製鉄","answer":["せいてつ"]},
    {"meaning":"conquest, subjugation, overcoming","question":"征服","answer":["せいふく"]},
    {"meaning":"manufacturing method, recipe, formula","question":"製法","answer":["せいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"precise, exact, detailed, minute, close","question":"精密","answer":["せいみつ"]},
    {"meaning":"full name","question":"姓名","answer":["せいめい"]},
    {"meaning":"influence, power, might, strength, potency, force, energy","question":"勢力","answer":["せいりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"stand in a row, form a line","question":"整列","answer":["せいれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"household","question":"世帯","answer":["せたい"]},
    {"meaning":"touch, contact","question":"接触","answer":["せっしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment, institution","question":"設置","answer":["せっち"]},
    {"meaning":"compromise, cross, blending, eclecticism","question":"折衷","answer":["せっちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment, creation","question":"設定","answer":["せってい"]},
    {"meaning":"conjunction","question":"接続詞","answer":["せつぞくし"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment, foundation, institution","question":"設立","answer":["せつりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"attack, offence","question":"攻め","answer":["せめ"]},
    {"meaning":"hermit, wizard","question":"仙","answer":["せん"]},
    {"meaning":"fibre, fiber, textile","question":"繊維","answer":["せんい"]},
    {"meaning":"election","question":"選挙","answer":["せんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"religious mission","question":"宣教","answer":["せんきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"declaration, proclamation, announcement","question":"宣言","answer":["せんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"war damage","question":"戦災","answer":["せんさい"]},
    {"meaning":"specialization","question":"専修","answer":["せんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"diving","question":"潜水","answer":["せんすい"]},
    {"meaning":"battle, fight, combat","question":"戦闘","answer":["せんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"infiltration, sneaking in","question":"潜入","answer":["せんにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"ship","question":"船舶","answer":["せんぱく"]},
    {"meaning":"exclusive use, personal use","question":"専用","answer":["せんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"occupation, capture, possession, have a room to oneself","question":"占領","answer":["せんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"tax office","question":"税務署","answer":["ぜいむしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"correction, revision","question":"是正","answer":["ぜせい"]},
    {"meaning":"out of print","question":"絶版","answer":["ぜっぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"Zen (Buddhism)","question":"禅","answer":["ぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"complete recovery of health","question":"全快","answer":["ぜんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"height of prosperity","question":"全盛","answer":["ぜんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"preamble, premise, reason, prerequisite","question":"前提","answer":["ぜんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"annihilation","question":"全滅","answer":["ぜんめつ"]},
    {"meaning":"goodness, excellence, virtue","question":"善良","answer":["ぜんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"monk, priest","question":"僧","answer":["そう"]},
    {"meaning":"to run along, to follow","question":"沿う","answer":["そう"]},
    {"meaning":"to accompany, to become married, to comply with","question":"添う","answer":["そう"]},
    {"meaning":"whole, all, general, gross","question":"総","answer":["そう","ふさ"]},
    {"meaning":"suitability, fitness","question":"相応","answer":["そうおう"]},
    {"meaning":"general meeting","question":"総会","answer":["そうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"launching (e.g. newspaper), first issue","question":"創刊","answer":["そうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"synthesis, coordination, putting together, integration, composite","question":"総合","answer":["そうごう"]},
    {"meaning":"search (esp. in criminal investigations), investigation","question":"捜査","answer":["そうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"search (esp. for someone or something missing), investigation","question":"捜索","answer":["そうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"ornament","question":"装飾","answer":["そうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"management, handling, control, manipulation","question":"操縦","answer":["そうじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"creation","question":"創造","answer":["そうぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"magnificent, grand, majestic, splendid","question":"壮大","answer":["そうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"strife, riot, rebellion","question":"騒動","answer":["そうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"disaster, shipwreck, accident","question":"遭難","answer":["そうなん"]},
    {"meaning":"equipment","question":"装備","answer":["そうび"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment, founding, organization","question":"創立","answer":["そうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to add to, to attach, to append, to accompany, to garnish, to imitate, to annex","question":"添える","answer":["そえる"]},
    {"meaning":"immediately, right away","question":"即座に","answer":["そくざに"]},
    {"meaning":"promotion, acceleration, encouragement, facilitation, spurring on","question":"促進","answer":["そくしん"]},
    {"meaning":"to conform to, to agree with, to be adapted to, to be based on","question":"即する","answer":["そくする"]},
    {"meaning":"restraint, shackles, restriction, confinement, binding","question":"束縛","answer":["そくばく"]},
    {"meaning":"to harm, to hurt, to injure, to damage, to fail in doing","question":"損なう","answer":["そこなう"]},
    {"meaning":"raw materials, subject matter","question":"素材","answer":["そざい"]},
    {"meaning":"obstruction, check, hindrance, prevention, interdiction","question":"阻止","answer":["そし"]},
    {"meaning":"litigation, lawsuit","question":"訴訟","answer":["そしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"measure, step","question":"措置","answer":["そち"]},
    {"meaning":"cold, short, curt, blunt","question":"素っ気ない","answer":["そっけない"]},
    {"meaning":"frankness, candour, openheartedness","question":"率直","answer":["そっちょく"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity, artlessness, naivete","question":"素朴","answer":["そぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dye","question":"染まる","answer":["そまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to dye, to colour","question":"染める","answer":["そめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn away, to avert","question":"逸らす","answer":["そらす"]},
    {"meaning":"each, every, either, respectively, severally","question":"各々","answer":["おのおの"]},
    {"meaning":"gradually, steadily, quietly, slowly, soon","question":"徐々","answer":["じょじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"loss","question":"損失","answer":["そんしつ"]},
    {"question":"蹴飛ばす","answer":["けとばす"],"meaning":"to kick away; to kick off; to kick hard, to refuse curtly; to reject outright"},
    {"meaning":"statue, image, figure, picture, portrait","question":"像","answer":["ぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"Minister of Finance","question":"蔵相","answer":["ぞうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"interaction, correspondence, coping with, dealing with","question":"対応","answer":["たいおう"]},
    {"meaning":"in general, mainly","question":"大概","answer":["たいがい"]},
    {"meaning":"treatment, reception","question":"待遇","answer":["たいぐう"]},
    {"meaning":"opposition, antagonism","question":"対抗","answer":["たいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"general public","question":"大衆","answer":["たいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"attitude, conditions, preparations","question":"態勢","answer":["たいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"non-payment, default","question":"滞納","answer":["たいのう"]},
    {"meaning":"contrast, comparison","question":"対比","answer":["たいひ"]},
    {"meaning":"(geometrical) opposite side","question":"対辺","answer":["たいへん"]},
    {"meaning":"negligence, procrastination, carelessness","question":"怠慢","answer":["たいまん"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear, to endure","question":"耐える","answer":["たえる"]},
    {"meaning":"many, a lot, much","question":"沢山","answer":["たくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"skill, cleverness","question":"巧み","answer":["たくみ"]},
    {"meaning":"addition","question":"足し算","answer":["たしざん"]},
    {"meaning":"to participate, to take part","question":"携わる","answer":["たずさわる"]},
    {"meaning":"to drift about, to float, to hang in air","question":"漂う","answer":["ただよう"]},
    {"meaning":"precious, valuable, priceless, noble, exalted, sacred","question":"尊い","answer":["とうとい","たっとい"]},
    {"meaning":"precious, valuable, priceless, noble, exalted, sacred","question":"貴い","answer":["たっとい","とうとい"]},
    {"question":"賭け","answer":["かけ"],"meaning":"betting; gambling; a gamble"},
    {"meaning":"shield, buckler, escutcheon, pretext","question":"盾","answer":["たて"]},
    {"meaning":"to offer, to present, to revere, to do respectfully","question":"奉る","answer":["たてまつる"]},
    {"question":"費やす","answer":["ついやす"],"meaning":"to spend; to expend; to consume, to waste; to squander; to throw away, to devote"},
    {"meaning":"transitive verb (direct obj)","question":"他動詞","answer":["たどうし"]},
    {"meaning":"the palm","question":"掌","answer":["たなごころ","てのひら"]},
    {"meaning":"intolerable, unbearable, unendurable","question":"堪らない","answer":["たまらない"]},
    {"meaning":"to grant, to bestow","question":"賜る","answer":["たまわる"]},
    {"meaning":"to keep, to preserve, to hold, to retain, to maintain, to support, to sustain, to last, to endure, to keep we","question":"保つ","answer":["たもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to hang, to droop, to drop, to lower, to pull down, to dangle, to sag, to drip, to ooze, to trickle, to leave","question":"垂れる","answer":["たれる"]},
    {"meaning":"tanka, 31-syllable Japanese poem","question":"短歌","answer":["たんか"]},
    {"meaning":"stretcher, litter","question":"担架","answer":["たんか"]},
    {"meaning":"quick temper","question":"短気","answer":["たんき"]},
    {"meaning":"exploration, expedition","question":"探検","answer":["たんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"shortening, abbreviation, reduction","question":"短縮","answer":["たんしゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"carbon (C)","question":"炭素","answer":["たんそ"]},
    {"meaning":"junior college","question":"短大","answer":["たんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"sole, independence, single, solo (flight)","question":"単独","answer":["たんどく"]},
    {"meaning":"short wave","question":"短波","answer":["たんぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"ordinal","question":"第","answer":["だい"]},
    {"meaning":"first, foremost, # 1","question":"第一","answer":["だいいち"]},
    {"meaning":"bold, daring, audacious","question":"大胆","answer":["だいたん"]},
    {"meaning":"pay by proxy, act for another, speak for another","question":"代弁","answer":["だいべん"]},
    {"meaning":"compromise, giving in","question":"妥協","answer":["だきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"agreement","question":"妥結","answer":["だけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"1. blow, shock, strike, damage, 2. batting (baseball)","question":"打撃","answer":["だげき"]},
    {"meaning":"poor work, rubbish","question":"駄作","answer":["ださく"]},
    {"meaning":"escape","question":"脱出","answer":["だっしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to escape from, to get out","question":"脱する","answer":["だっする"]},
    {"meaning":"secession","question":"脱退","answer":["だったい"]},
    {"question":"一様","answer":["いちよう"],"meaning":"uniformity; evenness; similarity; equality; impartiality; homogeneity"},
    {"meaning":"1. platform, podium, rostrum, 2. (arch) mandala","question":"壇","answer":["だん"]},
    {"meaning":"unity, union, combination","question":"団結","answer":["だんけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"master (of house), husband (informal)","question":"旦那","answer":["だんな"]},
    {"meaning":"elasticity, flexibility","question":"弾力","answer":["だんりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to pledge, to promise, to swear","question":"契る","answer":["ちぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"animal husbandry","question":"畜産","answer":["ちくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"beast, brute, damn","question":"畜生","answer":["ちくしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"accumulation, accumulate, store","question":"蓄積","answer":["ちくせき"]},
    {"meaning":"milk, breast, loop","question":"乳","answer":["ちち"]},
    {"meaning":"to be shortened, to be contracted, to shrink","question":"縮まる","answer":["ちぢまる"]},
    {"meaning":"suffocation","question":"窒息","answer":["ちっそく"]},
    {"meaning":"order, regularity, system, method","question":"秩序","answer":["ちつじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"landing, alighting, touch down","question":"着陸","answer":["ちゃくりく"]},
    {"meaning":"tea ceremony","question":"茶の湯","answer":["ちゃのゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"somersault, looping-the-loop","question":"宙返り","answer":["ちゅうがえり"]},
    {"meaning":"relay, hook-up","question":"中継","answer":["ちゅうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"advice, warning","question":"忠告","answer":["ちゅうこく"]},
    {"meaning":"slander, libel, defamation","question":"中傷","answer":["ちゅうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"fidelity, faithfulness","question":"忠実","answer":["ちゅうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"centre, pivot, mainstay, nucleus, backbone, central figure, pillar, key man","question":"中枢","answer":["ちゅうすう"]},
    {"meaning":"lottery, raffle, drawing (of lots)","question":"抽選","answer":["ちゅうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"poisoning","question":"中毒","answer":["ちゅうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"go-between, matchmaker","question":"仲人","answer":["ちゅうにん","なこうど"]},
    {"meaning":"guts, bowels, intestines","question":"腸","answer":["ちょう","わた"]},
    {"meaning":"butterfly","question":"蝶","answer":["ちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"super-, ultra-, hyper-","question":"超","answer":["ちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"government office","question":"庁","answer":["ちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"signature, sign, sealing","question":"調印","answer":["ちょういん"]},
    {"meaning":"the sense of hearing","question":"聴覚","answer":["ちょうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"lecture attendance, auditing","question":"聴講","answer":["ちょうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"collection, levy","question":"徴収","answer":["ちょうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"stethoscope","question":"聴診器","answer":["ちょうしんき"]},
    {"meaning":"challenge, defiance","question":"挑戦","answer":["ちょうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"arbitration, conciliation, mediation","question":"調停","answer":["ちょうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"long (e.g. novel film)","question":"長編","answer":["ちょうへん"]},
    {"meaning":"district of a town, city block (of irregular size)","question":"丁目","answer":["ちょうめ"]},
    {"meaning":"literary work, book","question":"著書","answer":["ちょしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"savings","question":"貯蓄","answer":["ちょちく"]},
    {"meaning":"well-known, noted, celebrated","question":"著名","answer":["ちょめい"]},
    {"meaning":"medical treatment","question":"治療","answer":["ちりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"wages","question":"賃金","answer":["ちんぎん"]},
    {"meaning":"precipitation, settlement","question":"沈殿","answer":["ちんでん"]},
    {"meaning":"sinking, foundering","question":"沈没","answer":["ちんぼつ"]},
    {"meaning":"silence, reticence","question":"沈黙","answer":["ちんもく"]},
    {"meaning":"exhibition, display, show","question":"陳列","answer":["ちんれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"gaining on, carrying out, solving (crime)","question":"追及","answer":["ついきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"pursuit","question":"追跡","answer":["ついせき"]},
    {"meaning":"falling, crashing","question":"墜落","answer":["ついらく"]},
    {"meaning":"mission, simple task, doing","question":"遣い","answer":["つかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to rule, to govern, to administer","question":"司る","answer":["つかさどる"]},
    {"meaning":"every month, common","question":"月並み","answer":["つきなみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be used up, to be run out, to be exhausted, to be consumed, to come to an end","question":"尽きる","answer":["つきる"]},
    {"meaning":"a joint, joining point","question":"継ぎ目","answer":["つぎめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to exhaust, to run out, to serve (a person), to befriend","question":"尽くす","answer":["つくす"]},
    {"meaning":"make up, structure, physique","question":"造り","answer":["つくり"]},
    {"question":"貴方","answer":["あなた"],"meaning":"your home; your residence, you (referring to one's equal; epistolary style), you (referring to someone of equal or lower status), dear (what a wife calls a husband), you"},
    {"meaning":"to mend, to repair, to fix, to patch up, to darn, to tidy up, to adjust, to trim","question":"繕う","answer":["つくろう"]},
    {"meaning":"to join, to piece together, to set (bones), to graft (trees)","question":"接ぐ","answer":["つぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to succeed","question":"継ぐ","answer":["つぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to support, to become stiff, to become taut, to thrust (ones opponent), to stick to (ones opinion), to in","question":"突っ張る","answer":["つっぱる"]},
    {"meaning":"pipe, tube","question":"筒","answer":["つつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be careful, to be chaste or discreet, to abstain or refrain","question":"慎む","answer":["つつしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"tsunami, tidal wave","question":"津波","answer":["つなみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to invite, to solicit help participation etc","question":"募る","answer":["つのる"]},
    {"meaning":"to pinch, to hold, to pick up","question":"摘む","answer":["つまむ","つむ"]},
    {"question":"貧困","answer":["ひんこん"],"meaning":"poor; needy, lacking; meagre; meager"},
    {"meaning":"dew","question":"露","answer":["つゆ","あらわ"]},
    {"meaning":"to go through","question":"貫く","answer":["つらぬく"]},
    {"question":"謀反","answer":["むほん"],"meaning":"rebellion; uprising; insurrection, treason, plotting to overthrow the government (by assassinating the emperor)"},
    {"meaning":"hanging bell","question":"釣鐘","answer":["つりがね"]},
    {"meaning":"offer, tender, program sponsoring, furnishing","question":"提供","answer":["ていきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"definition","question":"定義","answer":["ていぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"cooperation, tie-up, joint business, link-up","question":"提携","answer":["ていけい"]},
    {"meaning":"decency, style, form, appearance, show, get-up, format","question":"体裁","answer":["ていさい"]},
    {"meaning":"presentation, exhibit, suggest, citation","question":"提示","answer":["ていじ"]},
    {"meaning":"correction, revision","question":"訂正","answer":["ていせい"]},
    {"meaning":"stagnation, tie-up, congestion, retention, accumulation, falling into arrears","question":"停滞","answer":["ていたい"]},
    {"meaning":"mansion, residence","question":"邸宅","answer":["ていたく"]},
    {"meaning":"bank, weir","question":"堤防","answer":["ていぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"easy, simple, informal, offhand, cheap","question":"手軽","answer":["てがる"]},
    {"meaning":"adaptation, accommodation, conformity","question":"適応","answer":["てきおう"]},
    {"meaning":"suitability","question":"適宜","answer":["てきぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"process, procedure, protocol","question":"手順","answer":["てじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"handcuffs, manacles","question":"手錠","answer":["てじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"iron and steel","question":"鉄鋼","answer":["てっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"to sink in, to penetrate, to devote oneself, to believe in, to go through, to do intently and exclusively","question":"徹する","answer":["てっする"]},
    {"meaning":"iron scraps","question":"鉄片","answer":["てっぺん"]},
    {"meaning":"to reflect, to throw back light","question":"照り返す","answer":["てりかえす"]},
    {"meaning":"convert, divert","question":"転換","answer":["てんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"inspection, examination, checking","question":"点検","answer":["てんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"natural calamity, disaster","question":"天災","answer":["てんさい"]},
    {"meaning":"exhibition, display","question":"展示","answer":["てんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"ceiling, ceiling price","question":"天井","answer":["てんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"dotted line, perforated line","question":"点線","answer":["てんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"view, outlook, prospect","question":"展望","answer":["てんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"source of electricity, power (button on TV etc.)","question":"電源","answer":["でんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"electric line","question":"電線","answer":["でんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"place, section, building","question":"棟","answer":["とう","むね"]},
    {"meaning":"pottery, ceramics","question":"陶器","answer":["とうき"]},
    {"meaning":"grade, class","question":"等級","answer":["とうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"debate, discussion","question":"討議","answer":["とうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"integration, unification, synthesis","question":"統合","answer":["とうごう"]},
    {"meaning":"rule, reign, government, governing","question":"統治","answer":["とうじ","とうち"]},
    {"meaning":"regulation, control","question":"統制","answer":["とうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"command, lead, generalship, leadership","question":"統率","answer":["とうそつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(cannot) possibly","question":"到底","answer":["とうてい"]},
    {"question":"説く","answer":["とく"],"meaning":"to explain; to advocate; to preach; to persuade"},
    {"meaning":"registration, register, entry, record","question":"登録","answer":["とうろく"]},
    {"meaning":"debate, discussion","question":"討論","answer":["とうろん"]},
    {"meaning":"to pause, to be interrupted","question":"跡切れる","answer":["とぎれる"]},
    {"meaning":"special skill","question":"特技","answer":["とくぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"send specially, special envoy","question":"特派","answer":["とくは"]},
    {"meaning":"thorn, splinter, spine, biting words","question":"刺","answer":["とげ","し"]},
    {"meaning":"to accomplish, to achieve, to carry out","question":"遂げる","answer":["とげる"]},
    {"question":"誤差","answer":["ごさ"],"meaning":"measurement error; calculation error"},
    {"meaning":"closing up, fastening the doors","question":"戸締り","answer":["とじまり"]},
    {"meaning":"suddenly, all of a sudden","question":"突如","answer":["とつじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to put in order, to get ready, to arrange, to adjust","question":"整える","answer":["ととのえる"]},
    {"meaning":"report, notification, registration","question":"届け","answer":["とどけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to stagnate, to be delayed","question":"滞る","answer":["とどこおる"]},
    {"meaning":"to recite, to chant, to call upon","question":"唱える","answer":["となえる"]},
    {"meaning":"feudal lord","question":"殿様","answer":["とのさま"]},
    {"meaning":"curtain","question":"帳","answer":["とばり"]},
    {"meaning":"door, opening","question":"扉","answer":["とびら"]},
    {"meaning":"meagre, scarce, limited, destitute, hard up, scanty, poor","question":"乏しい","answer":["とぼしい"]},
    {"meaning":"working together, (husband and wife) earning a living together","question":"共稼ぎ","answer":["ともかせぎ"]},
    {"question":"誤る","answer":["あやまる"],"meaning":"to make a mistake; to err, to mislead; to misguide"},
    {"meaning":"to accompany, to bring with, to be accompanied by, to be involved in","question":"伴う","answer":["ともなう"]},
    {"meaning":"treatment, service, handling, management","question":"取り扱い","answer":["とりあつかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to treat, to handle, to deal in","question":"取り扱う","answer":["とりあつかう"]},
    {"meaning":"swap, exchange","question":"取り替え","answer":["とりかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"control, management, supervision","question":"取り締まり","answer":["とりしまり"]},
    {"meaning":"to manage, to control, to supervise","question":"取り締まる","answer":["とりしまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to surround, to circle, to enclose","question":"取り巻く","answer":["とりまく"]},
    {"meaning":"to mix, to put together","question":"取り混ぜる","answer":["とりまぜる"]},
    {"meaning":"especially, above all","question":"副","answer":["ふく"]},
    {"meaning":"trunk, body, frame","question":"胴","answer":["どう"]},
    {"meaning":"the same grade, same class","question":"同級","answer":["どうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"fellow, companion, comrade","question":"同士","answer":["どうし"]},
    {"meaning":"same mind, comrade, kindred soul","question":"同志","answer":["どうし"]},
    {"meaning":"introduction, bringing in, leading in","question":"導入","answer":["どうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"enclosure (e.g. in a letter)","question":"同封","answer":["どうふう"]},
    {"meaning":"alliance, union, league","question":"同盟","answer":["どうめい"]},
    {"meaning":"disturbance, unrest, shaking, trembling, pitching, rolling, oscillation, agitation, excitement, commotion","question":"動揺","answer":["どうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"dictatorship, despotism","question":"独裁","answer":["どくさい"]},
    {"meaning":"original, peculiar, characteristic","question":"独自","answer":["どくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"monopoly","question":"独占","answer":["どくせん"]},
    {"meaning":"originality","question":"独創","answer":["どくそう"]},
    {"meaning":"arena","question":"土俵","answer":["どひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"thickheadedness, stolidity","question":"鈍感","answer":["どんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"cabinet, (government) ministry","question":"内閣","answer":["ないかく"]},
    {"meaning":"internal organs, intestines, viscera","question":"内臓","answer":["ないぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"civil war, insurrection, rebellion, domestic conflict","question":"内乱","answer":["ないらん"]},
    {"meaning":"inland","question":"内陸","answer":["ないりく"]},
    {"meaning":"rice seedling","question":"苗","answer":["なえ"]},
    {"meaning":"furthermore, still, yet, more, still more, greater, further, less","question":"尚","answer":["なお"]},
    {"meaning":"to strike, to hit","question":"殴る","answer":["なぐる"]},
    {"meaning":"to sigh, to lament, to grieve","question":"嘆く","answer":["なげく"]},
    {"meaning":"avalanche","question":"雪崩","answer":["なだれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to become emotionally attached","question":"懐く","answer":["なつく"]},
    {"question":"語彙","answer":["ごい"],"meaning":"vocabulary; lexicon; lexis; terminology"},
    {"meaning":"name plate, name tag","question":"名札","answer":["なふだ"]},
    {"meaning":"smelling of fish or blood, fish or meat","question":"生臭い","answer":["なまぐさい"]},
    {"meaning":"lukewarm, halfhearted","question":"生温い","answer":["なまぬるい"]},
    {"meaning":"lead (the metal)","question":"鉛","answer":["なまり"]},
    {"meaning":"to become less capable, to grow dull, to become blunt, to weaken","question":"鈍る","answer":["なまる","にぶる"]},
    {"meaning":"average, medium, common, ordinary","question":"並み","answer":["なみ"]},
    {"meaning":"smoothness, glassiness","question":"滑らか","answer":["なめらか"]},
    {"meaning":"seductive, melancholy, languid","question":"悩ましい","answer":["なやましい"]},
    {"meaning":"to afflict, to torment, to harass, to molest","question":"悩ます","answer":["なやます"]},
    {"meaning":"trouble(s), worry, distress, anguish, agony, problem","question":"悩み","answer":["なやみ"]},
    {"question":"詰る","answer":["なじる"],"meaning":"to rebuke; to scold; to tell off"},
    {"meaning":"and","question":"並びに","answer":["ならびに"]},
    {"meaning":"load, baggage, cargo","question":"荷","answer":["に"]},
    {"meaning":"hatred","question":"憎しみ","answer":["にくしみ"]},
    {"meaning":"packing, baling, crating","question":"荷造り","answer":["にづくり"]},
    {"meaning":"to carry on shoulder, to bear (burden), to shoulder (gun)","question":"担う","answer":["になう"]},
    {"question":"試みる","answer":["こころみる"],"meaning":"to try; to attempt; to have a go (at something)"},
    {"meaning":"winning a prize or place (in a contest)","question":"入賞","answer":["にゅうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"bathe, bathing","question":"入浴","answer":["にゅうよく"]},
    {"meaning":"urine","question":"尿","answer":["にょう"]},
    {"meaning":"conception, pregnancy","question":"妊娠","answer":["にんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"swamp, bog, pond, lake","question":"沼","answer":["ぬま"]},
    {"meaning":"boiling water","question":"熱湯","answer":["ねっとう"]},
    {"meaning":"temperature","question":"熱量","answer":["ねつりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"stickyness, viscosity","question":"粘り","answer":["ねばり"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sticky, to be adhesive, to persevere, to persist, to stick to","question":"粘る","answer":["ねばる"]},
    {"meaning":"making necessary arrangements","question":"根回し","answer":["ねまわし"]},
    {"meaning":"to knead, to work over, to polish up","question":"練る","answer":["ねる"]},
    {"meaning":"yearbook","question":"年鑑","answer":["ねんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"burning, combustion","question":"燃焼","answer":["ねんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"fuel","question":"燃料","answer":["ねんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"annual tree ring","question":"年輪","answer":["ねんりん"]},
    {"meaning":"brain, memory","question":"脳","answer":["のう"]},
    {"meaning":"farming, agriculture","question":"農耕","answer":["のうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"farm (agriculture)","question":"農場","answer":["のうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"agricultural land","question":"農地","answer":["のうち"]},
    {"meaning":"payment, supply","question":"納入","answer":["のうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"row of houses","question":"軒並み","answer":["のきなみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to look out on, to face, to deal with, to attend (function)","question":"臨む","answer":["のぞむ"]},
    {"meaning":"futures, credit (buying), stretching, total","question":"延べ","answer":["のべ"]},
    {"meaning":"(n) transfer (trains, buses, etc.)","question":"乗り換え","answer":["のりかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"edge (of a sword)","question":"刃","answer":["は","やいば"]},
    {"meaning":"clique, faction, school","question":"派","answer":["は"]},
    {"meaning":"grasp, catch, understanding","question":"把握","answer":["はあく"]},
    {"meaning":"lung","question":"肺","answer":["はい"]},
    {"meaning":"annullment, disposal, abandon, scrap, discarding, repeal","question":"廃棄","answer":["はいき"]},
    {"meaning":"Dear (so and so)","question":"拝啓","answer":["はいけい"]},
    {"meaning":"abolition, repeal","question":"廃止","answer":["はいし"]},
    {"meaning":"borrowing","question":"拝借","answer":["はいしゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"exclusion, removal, rejection","question":"排除","answer":["はいじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"drainage","question":"排水","answer":["はいすい"]},
    {"meaning":"distribution","question":"配布","answer":["はいふ"]},
    {"meaning":"consideration, concern, forethought","question":"配慮","answer":["はいりょ"]},
    {"meaning":"destruction","question":"破壊","answer":["はかい"]},
    {"meaning":"cemetery, graveyard","question":"墓地","answer":["はかち","ぼち"]},
    {"meaning":"to consult with, to confer","question":"諮る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"revocation, annulment, breaking (e.g. treaty)","question":"破棄","answer":["はき"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for nights of a stay","question":"泊","answer":["はく"]},
    {"meaning":"persecution","question":"迫害","answer":["はくがい"]},
    {"meaning":"feebleness, weakness, weak","question":"薄弱","answer":["はくじゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"dispatch, send","question":"派遣","answer":["はけん"]},
    {"meaning":"to encourage, to cheer, to raise (the voice)","question":"励ます","answer":["はげます"]},
    {"meaning":"to be zealous, to brace oneself, to endeavour, to strive, to make an effort","question":"励む","answer":["はげむ"]},
    {"meaning":"pillar, post","question":"柱","answer":["はしら"]},
    {"meaning":"bridge building, mediation","question":"橋渡し","answer":["はしわたし"]},
    {"meaning":"to spring, to bound, to bounce, to be stimulated, to be encouraged, to get lively, to treat oneself to, to","question":"弾む","answer":["はずむ"]},
    {"meaning":"damage","question":"破損","answer":["はそん"]},
    {"meaning":"barefoot","question":"裸足","answer":["はだし"]},
    {"meaning":"excavation, exhumation","question":"発掘","answer":["はっくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"burgeoning","question":"発芽","answer":["はつが"]},
    {"meaning":"brilliant, magnificent, spectacular","question":"華々しい","answer":["はなばなしい"]},
    {"meaning":"gay, showy, brilliant, gorgeous, florid","question":"華やか","answer":["はなやか"]},
    {"meaning":"to keep someone from doing, to stop, to prevent, to check, to hinder, to obstruct, to oppose, to thwart","question":"阻む","answer":["はばむ"]},
    {"meaning":"beach, seashore","question":"浜","answer":["はま"]},
    {"meaning":"beach, foreshore","question":"浜辺","answer":["はまべ"]},
    {"meaning":"dentifrice, toothpaste","question":"歯磨","answer":["はみがき"]},
    {"meaning":"paper patch, paper backing, poster","question":"張り紙","answer":["はりがみ"]},
    {"meaning":"far, far-away, distant, remote, far off","question":"遥か","answer":["はるか"]},
    {"meaning":"explosion, rupture, break off","question":"破裂","answer":["はれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"group, party, section (mil)","question":"班","answer":["はん"]},
    {"meaning":"edition","question":"版","answer":["はん","ばん"]},
    {"meaning":"prospering, prosperity, thriving, flourishing","question":"繁栄","answer":["はんえい"]},
    {"meaning":"art print","question":"版画","answer":["はんが"]},
    {"meaning":"echo, reverberation, repercussion, reaction, influence","question":"反響","answer":["はんきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"counterattack, counteroffensive, counterblow","question":"反撃","answer":["はんげき"]},
    {"meaning":"reflection, reverberation","question":"反射","answer":["はんしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"breed, multiply, increase, propagation","question":"繁殖","answer":["はんしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"prosperity, flourishing, thriving","question":"繁盛","answer":["はんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"reaction, response","question":"反応","answer":["はんのう"]},
    {"meaning":"remnant, fragment, incomplete set, fraction, odd sum, incompleteness","question":"半端","answer":["はんぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"insurrection, mutiny, rebellion, revolt, uprising","question":"反乱","answer":["はんらん"]},
    {"meaning":"bacteria, germ(s)","question":"ばい菌","answer":["ばいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"reparations, indemnity, compensation","question":"賠償","answer":["ばいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"diameter, magnification","question":"倍率","answer":["ばいりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"stupid","question":"馬鹿馬鹿しい","answer":["ばかばかしい"]},
    {"meaning":"absurd","question":"馬鹿らしい","answer":["ばからしい"]},
    {"meaning":"obscure, vague, equivocal","question":"漠然","answer":["ばくぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"bomb","question":"爆弾","answer":["ばくだん"]},
    {"meaning":"blast, explosion, blow up","question":"爆破","answer":["ばくは"]},
    {"meaning":"disclosure, exposure, revelation","question":"暴露","answer":["ばくろ"]},
    {"meaning":"(divine) punishment, curse, retribution","question":"罰","answer":["ばち","ばつ"]},
    {"meaning":"waiting room","question":"控室","answer":["ひかえしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to draw in, to hold back, to make notes, to be temperate in","question":"控える","answer":["ひかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"head, small animal counter, roll of cloth","question":"匹","answer":["ひき"]},
    {"meaning":"to lead, to spearhead (a group), to command (troops)","question":"率いる","answer":["ひきいる"]},
    {"meaning":"long, long-continued, old (story)","question":"久しい","answer":["ひさしい"]},
    {"meaning":"after a long time","question":"久し振り","answer":["ひさしぶり"]},
    {"meaning":"misery","question":"悲惨","answer":["ひさん"]},
    {"meaning":"(private) secretary","question":"秘書","answer":["ひしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"specific gravity","question":"比重","answer":["ひじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"secret, private, surreptitious","question":"密か","answer":["ひそか"]},
    {"meaning":"to soak, to dip, to drench","question":"浸す","answer":["ひたす"]},
    {"meaning":"required (subject)","question":"必修","answer":["ひっしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"comparing with, match, rival, equal","question":"匹敵","answer":["ひってき"]},
    {"meaning":"personality, character, personal appearance, gentility","question":"人柄","answer":["ひとがら"]},
    {"meaning":"a line, earnestly, blindly, straightforwardly","question":"一筋","answer":["ひとすじ"]},
    {"meaning":"cruel, awful, severe, very bad, serious, terrible, heavy, violent","question":"酷い","answer":["ひどい"]},
    {"question":"一羽","answer":["いちわ"],"meaning":"one (bird)"},
    {"meaning":"taking refuge, finding shelter","question":"避難","answer":["ひなん"]},
    {"meaning":"the Japanese flag","question":"日の丸","answer":["ひのまる"]},
    {"meaning":"encyclopedia","question":"百科事典","answer":["ひゃっかじてん"]},
    {"meaning":"encyclopedia","question":"百科辞典","answer":["ひゃっかじてん"]},
    {"meaning":"sunburn","question":"日焼け","answer":["ひやけ"]},
    {"meaning":"label, ballot, ticket, sign","question":"票","answer":["ひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"motto, slogan, catchword","question":"標語","answer":["ひょうご"]},
    {"meaning":"ratio, proportion, percentage","question":"比率","answer":["ひりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"manure, fertilizer","question":"肥料","answer":["ひりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"proportion","question":"比例","answer":["ひれい"]},
    {"meaning":"poor, meagre, insubstantial","question":"貧弱","answer":["ひんじゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"frequency","question":"頻繁","answer":["ひんぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"smile","question":"微笑","answer":["びしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"depiction, description, portrayal","question":"描写","answer":["びょうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"minuscule amount, extremely small quantity","question":"微量","answer":["びりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sensibility, susceptibility, sensitive (to), well attuned to","question":"敏感","answer":["びんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"poverty, destitute, poor","question":"貧乏","answer":["びんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"seal","question":"封","answer":["ふう"]},
    {"meaning":"blockade, freezing (funds)","question":"封鎖","answer":["ふうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"1. manners, customs, 2. sex service, sex industry","question":"風俗","answer":["ふうぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"ominous, sinister, bad luck, ill omen, inauspiciousness","question":"不吉","answer":["ふきつ"]},
    {"meaning":"recession, depression, slump","question":"不況","answer":["ふきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"restoration, restitution, rehabilitation","question":"復旧","answer":["ふくきゅう","ふっきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"composite, complex","question":"複合","answer":["ふくごう"]},
    {"meaning":"welfare, well-being","question":"福祉","answer":["ふくし"]},
    {"meaning":"mask, veil, disguise","question":"覆面","answer":["ふくめん"]},
    {"meaning":"to get cross, to get sulky, to swell (out), to expand, to be inflated, to distend, to bulge","question":"膨れる","answer":["ふくれる"]},
    {"meaning":"edict, ordinance, proclamation","question":"布告","answer":["ふこく"]},
    {"meaning":"wealthy person, millionaire","question":"富豪","answer":["ふごう"]},
    {"meaning":"debt, liabilities","question":"負債","answer":["ふさい"]},
    {"meaning":"injury, wound","question":"負傷","answer":["ふしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"incomplete understanding, doubt, question, distrust, suspicion, strangeness, infidelity","question":"不審","answer":["ふしん"]},
    {"meaning":"dullness, depression, slump, stagnation","question":"不振","answer":["ふしん"]},
    {"meaning":"irregularity, unseasonableness","question":"不順","answer":["ふじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"attached, belonging, affiliated, annexed, associated, subordinate, incidental, dependent, auxiliary","question":"付属","answer":["ふぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"burden, charge, responsibility","question":"負担","answer":["ふたん"]},
    {"meaning":"revival (e.g. musical), restoration","question":"復活","answer":["ふっかつ"]},
    {"meaning":"revival, renaissance, reconstruction","question":"復興","answer":["ふっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"boiling, seething","question":"沸騰","answer":["ふっとう"]},
    {"meaning":"Buddha, merciful person, Buddhist image, the dead","question":"仏","answer":["ほとけ","ふつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(proceeding to) new appointment","question":"赴任","answer":["ふにん"]},
    {"meaning":"decay, depravity","question":"腐敗","answer":["ふはい"]},
    {"meaning":"bad reputation, disgrace, unpopularity","question":"不評","answer":["ふひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"universality, ubiquity, omnipresence","question":"普遍","answer":["ふへん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be based on, to have origin in","question":"踏まえる","answer":["ふまえる"]},
    {"meaning":"support, maintenance","question":"扶養","answer":["ふよう"]},
    {"meaning":"pretence, show, appearance","question":"振り","answer":["ふり"]},
    {"meaning":"outset, starting point, drawing or issuing (draft)","question":"振り出し","answer":["ふりだし"]},
    {"meaning":"to be shaking, to be trembling","question":"震わせる","answer":["ふるわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"appendix, supplement","question":"付録","answer":["ふろく"]},
    {"meaning":"indignation, resentment","question":"憤慨","answer":["ふんがい"]},
    {"meaning":"losing something","question":"紛失","answer":["ふんしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"spewing, gushing, spouting, eruption, effusion","question":"噴出","answer":["ふんしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"dispute, trouble, strife","question":"紛争","answer":["ふんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"hard struggle, strenuous effort","question":"奮闘","answer":["ふんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"fine powder","question":"粉末","answer":["ふんまつ"]},
    {"meaning":"insult, contempt, slight","question":"侮辱","answer":["ぶじょく"]},
    {"meaning":"arms, armament, armed","question":"武装","answer":["ぶそう"]},
    {"meaning":"Buddhist image (statue)","question":"仏像","answer":["ぶつぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"class, group, category, department, field, branch","question":"部門","answer":["ぶもん"]},
    {"meaning":"armed might, military power, the sword, force","question":"武力","answer":["ぶりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"arms, weapons, ordinance","question":"兵器","answer":["へいき"]},
    {"meaning":"closing, closure, shutdown, lockout, unsociable","question":"閉鎖","answer":["へいさ"]},
    {"meaning":"soldier","question":"兵士","answer":["へいし"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement, parallel, abreast","question":"並列","answer":["へいれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be distant","question":"隔たる","answer":["へだたる"]},
    {"meaning":"compilation, editing, completed poem, book, part of book","question":"編","answer":["へん"]},
    {"meaning":"side, left radical of a character, inclining, inclining toward, biased","question":"偏","answer":["へん"]},
    {"meaning":"change, reform, revolution, upheaval, (the) Reformation","question":"変革","answer":["へんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"return, restoration","question":"返還","answer":["へんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"prejudice, narrow view","question":"偏見","answer":["へんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"change, transition, vicissitudes","question":"変遷","answer":["へんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"explanation, justification, defence, excuse","question":"弁解","answer":["べんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"convenience, accommodation, advantage, expedience","question":"便宜","answer":["べんぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"defense, pleading, advocacy","question":"弁護","answer":["べんご"]},
    {"meaning":"next word, compensation, reparation, indemnity, reimbursement","question":"弁償","answer":["べんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"discussion, debate, argument","question":"弁論","answer":["べんろん"]},
    {"meaning":"ear (of plant), head (of plant)","question":"穂","answer":["ほ"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing, nurturing, rearing, lactation, suckling","question":"保育","answer":["ほいく"]},
    {"meaning":"bill (law)","question":"法案","answer":["ほうあん"]},
    {"meaning":"collapse, decay (physics), crumbling, breaking down, caving in","question":"崩壊","answer":["ほうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"abandonment, renunciation, abdication (responsibility right)","question":"放棄","answer":["ほうき"]},
    {"meaning":"treasured article or vessel, outstanding individual","question":"宝器","answer":["ほうき"]},
    {"meaning":"feudalistic","question":"封建","answer":["ほうけん"]},
    {"meaning":"abundant harvest, bumper crop","question":"豊作","answer":["ほうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"plan, policy","question":"方策","answer":["ほうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"attendance, service","question":"奉仕","answer":["ほうし"]},
    {"meaning":"radiation, emission","question":"放射","answer":["ほうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"radioactivity","question":"放射能","answer":["ほうしゃのう"]},
    {"meaning":"remuneration, recompense, reward, toll","question":"報酬","answer":["ほうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"courtroom","question":"法廷","answer":["ほうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"reward, prize","question":"褒美","answer":["ほうび"]},
    {"meaning":"to bury, to inter, to entomb, to consign to oblivion, to shelve","question":"葬る","answer":["ほうむる"]},
    {"meaning":"saturation","question":"飽和","answer":["ほうわ"]},
    {"meaning":"retaining warmth, keeping heat in, heat insulation","question":"保温","answer":["ほおん"]},
    {"meaning":"capture, seizure","question":"捕獲","answer":["ほかく"]},
    {"meaning":"charge, custody, safekeeping, deposit, storage","question":"保管","answer":["ほかん"]},
    {"meaning":"supply, supplying, replenishment","question":"補給","answer":["ほきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"compensation, reinforcement","question":"補強","answer":["ほきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"insurance, guarantee","question":"保険","answer":["ほけん"]},
    {"meaning":"whaling, whale fishing","question":"捕鯨","answer":["ほげい"]},
    {"meaning":"to boast of, to be proud of","question":"誇る","answer":["ほこる"]},
    {"meaning":"care, protection, shelter, guardianship, favor, patronage","question":"保護","answer":["ほご"]},
    {"meaning":"dried washing (clothes)","question":"干し物","answer":["ほしもの"]},
    {"meaning":"conservative, maintaining","question":"保守","answer":["ほしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"guarantee, security, assurance, pledge, warranty","question":"保障","answer":["ほしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"compensation, reparation","question":"補償","answer":["ほしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"supplementation, supplement, replenishment, replenishing","question":"補充","answer":["ほじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"assistance, support, aid, auxiliary","question":"補助","answer":["ほじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"pavement, road surface","question":"舗装","answer":["ほそう"]},
    {"meaning":"supplement, complement","question":"補足","answer":["ほそく"]},
    {"question":"記す","answer":["しるす"],"meaning":"to write down; to note; to jot down, to remember"},
    {"meaning":"to donate, to give, to conduct, to apply, to perform","question":"施す","answer":["ほどこす"]},
    {"meaning":"day care worker in a kindergarten nursery school etc.","question":"保母","answer":["ほぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"health preservation, recuperation, recreation","question":"保養","answer":["ほよう"]},
    {"meaning":"constable","question":"捕吏","answer":["ほり"]},
    {"meaning":"prisoner (of war)","question":"捕虜","answer":["ほりょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be ruined, to go under, to perish, to be destroyed","question":"滅びる","answer":["ほろびる"]},
    {"meaning":"to destroy, to overthrow, to wreck, to ruin","question":"滅ぼす","answer":["ほろぼす"]},
    {"meaning":"defense, protection, self-defense","question":"防衛","answer":["ぼうえい"]},
    {"meaning":"fire prevention, fire fighting, fire proof","question":"防火","answer":["ぼうか"]},
    {"meaning":"disturbance, obstruction, hindrance, jamming, interference","question":"妨害","answer":["ぼうがい"]},
    {"meaning":"spinning","question":"紡績","answer":["ぼうせき"]},
    {"meaning":"expansion, swelling, increase, growth","question":"膨脹","answer":["ぼうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"beginning, start, outset","question":"冒頭","answer":["ぼうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"insurrection, rebellion, revolt, riot, uprising","question":"暴動","answer":["ぼうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"storm, windstorm, gale","question":"暴風","answer":["ぼうふう"]},
    {"meaning":"violence","question":"暴力","answer":["ぼうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"fund-raising, collection of funds","question":"募金","answer":["ぼきん"]},
    {"meaning":"pastor, minister, clergyman","question":"牧師","answer":["ぼくし"]},
    {"meaning":"forfeited","question":"没収","answer":["ぼっしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"ruin, fall, collapse","question":"没落","answer":["ぼつらく"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for flat objects (e.g. sheets of paper)","question":"枚","answer":["まい"]},
    {"meaning":"buried property, treasure trove","question":"埋蔵","answer":["まいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"to give board to, to provide meals, to pay","question":"賄う","answer":["まかなう"]},
    {"meaning":"volume","question":"巻","answer":["まき"]},
    {"meaning":"confusing, misleading, equivocal, ambiguous","question":"紛らわしい","answer":["まぎらわしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be diverted, to slip into","question":"紛れる","answer":["まぎれる"]},
    {"meaning":"membrane, film","question":"膜","answer":["まく"]},
    {"meaning":"truth, faith, fidelity, sincerity, trust, confidence, reliance, devotion","question":"誠","answer":["まこと"]},
    {"meaning":"anaesthesia","question":"麻酔","answer":["ますい"]},
    {"meaning":"wink, twinkling (of stars), flicker (of light)","question":"瞬き","answer":["またたき", "まばたき"]},
    {"meaning":"to escape from, to be rescued from, to avoid, to evade, to avert, to elude, to be exempted, to be relieved","question":"免れる","answer":["まぬかれる","まぬがれる"]},
    {"meaning":"eyebrow","question":"眉","answer":["まゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"ball","question":"鞠","answer":["まり"]},
    {"meaning":"completely","question":"丸々","answer":["まるまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to make round, to round off, to roll up, to curl up, to seduce, to cajole, to explain away","question":"丸める","answer":["まるめる"]},
    {"meaning":"perfectly circular","question":"真ん丸い","answer":["まんまるい"]},
    {"meaning":"miserable","question":"惨め","answer":["みじめ"]},
    {"meaning":"inexperience, unripeness, raw, unskilled, immature, inexperienced","question":"未熟","answer":["みじゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw out of order, to disarrange, to disturb","question":"乱す","answer":["みだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to get confused, to be disordered, to be disturbed","question":"乱れる","answer":["みだれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be guided, to be shown","question":"導く","answer":["みちびく"]},
    {"meaning":"crowd, close formation, dense","question":"密集","answer":["みっしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"related, connected, close, intimate","question":"密接","answer":["みっせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"density","question":"密度","answer":["みつど"]},
    {"meaning":"source, origin","question":"源","answer":["みなもと"]},
    {"meaning":"peak, ridge","question":"峰","answer":["みね"]},
    {"meaning":"pulse","question":"脈","answer":["みゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"lingering affection, attachment, regret(s), reluctance","question":"未練","answer":["みれん"]},
    {"meaning":"people, race, nation, racial customs, folk customs","question":"民俗","answer":["みんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"son-in-law","question":"婿","answer":["むこ"]},
    {"meaning":"ending, conclusion, union","question":"結び","answer":["むすび"]},
    {"meaning":"connection, relation","question":"結び付き","answer":["むすびつき"]},
    {"meaning":"to be connected or related, to join together","question":"結び付く","answer":["むすびつく"]},
    {"meaning":"to combine, to join, to tie on, to attach with a knot","question":"結び付ける","answer":["むすびつける"]},
    {"meaning":"to swarm, to gather","question":"群がる","answer":["むらがる"]},
    {"meaning":"name","question":"名称","answer":["めいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"register of names","question":"名簿","answer":["めいぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"honor, credit, prestige","question":"名誉","answer":["めいよ"]},
    {"meaning":"clarity","question":"明瞭","answer":["めいりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"bright, clear, cheerful","question":"明朗","answer":["めいろう"]},
    {"meaning":"blessing","question":"恵み","answer":["めぐみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to bless, to show mercy to","question":"恵む","answer":["めぐむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to call, to send for, to put on, to wear, to take (a bath), to ride in, to buy, to eat, to drink, to catch (a","question":"召す","answer":["めす"]},
    {"meaning":"female (animal)","question":"雌","answer":["めす"]},
    {"meaning":"absurd, unreasonable, excessive, messed up, spoiled, wreaked","question":"滅茶苦茶","answer":["めちゃくちゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"downfall, ruin, collapse, destruction","question":"滅亡","answer":["めつぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"scale, gradations","question":"目盛り","answer":["めもり"]},
    {"meaning":"exemption, exoneration, discharge","question":"免除","answer":["めんじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to create, to establish","question":"設ける","answer":["もうける"]},
    {"meaning":"blind spot","question":"盲点","answer":["もうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"violent, vehement, rage","question":"猛烈","answer":["もうれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"catalogue, catalog, list","question":"目録","answer":["もくろく"]},
    {"meaning":"model, dummy, maquette","question":"模型","answer":["もけい"]},
    {"meaning":"groping (for)","question":"模索","answer":["もさく"]},
    {"meaning":"exemplar, exemplification, exemplum, model, example","question":"模範","answer":["もはん"]},
    {"meaning":"imitation, copying","question":"模倣","answer":["もほう"]},
    {"meaning":"to hold (a meeting), to give (a dinner), to feel, to show signs of, to develop symptoms of, to feel (sick","question":"催す","answer":["もよおす"]},
    {"meaning":"to let leak, to reveal","question":"漏らす","answer":["もらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to rouse, to swell, to rise","question":"盛り上がる","answer":["もりあがる"]},
    {"meaning":"to leak, to run out","question":"漏る","answer":["もる"]},
    {"meaning":"to leak out, to escape, to come through, to shine through, to filter out, to be omitted","question":"漏れる","answer":["もれる"]},
    {"meaning":"arrow","question":"矢","answer":["や"]},
    {"question":"討伐","answer":["とうばつ"],"meaning":"subjugation; suppression"},
    {"meaning":"mansion","question":"屋敷","answer":["やしき"]},
    {"meaning":"to rear, to maintain, to cultivate","question":"養う","answer":["やしなう"]},
    {"meaning":"dude, servant, fellow","question":"奴","answer":["やつ","やっこ"]},
    {"meaning":"opposition party","question":"野党","answer":["やとう"]},
    {"meaning":"to carry through, to achieve, to complete","question":"遣り通す","answer":["やりとおす"]},
    {"meaning":"to accomplish","question":"やり遂げる","answer":["やりとげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to do, to have sexual intercourse, to kill, to give (to inferiors animals etc.), to dispatch (a letter","question":"遣る","answer":["やる"]},
    {"meaning":"beneficial, profitable","question":"有益","answer":["ゆうえき"]},
    {"meaning":"bravery, heroism, gallantry","question":"勇敢","answer":["ゆうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"financing, loan","question":"融資","answer":["ゆうし"]},
    {"meaning":"lending (money), accommodation, adaptability, versatility, finance","question":"融通","answer":["ゆうずう","ゆうづう"]},
    {"meaning":"superiority, superior power, predominance, preponderance","question":"優勢","answer":["ゆうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"guidance, leading, induction, introduction, incitement, inducement","question":"誘導","answer":["ゆうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"nomadism","question":"遊牧","answer":["ゆうぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"sunset","question":"夕焼け","answer":["ゆうやけ"]},
    {"meaning":"ghost, specter, apparition, phantom","question":"幽霊","answer":["ゆうれい"]},
    {"meaning":"temptation, allurement, lure","question":"誘惑","answer":["ゆうわく"]},
    {"meaning":"to shake, to jolt, to rock, to swing","question":"揺さぶる","answer":["ゆさぶる"]},
    {"meaning":"bow (and arrow)","question":"弓","answer":["ゆみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to swing, to sway, to shake, to tremble","question":"揺らぐ","answer":["ゆらぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to become loose, to slacken","question":"緩む","answer":["ゆるむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to loosen, to slow down","question":"緩める","answer":["ゆるめる"]},
    {"meaning":"lenient","question":"緩やか","answer":["ゆるやか"]},
    {"meaning":"solution (liquid)","question":"溶液","answer":["ようえき"]},
    {"meaning":"protection, nursing, protective care","question":"養護","answer":["ようご"]},
    {"meaning":"claim, demand, request, application","question":"要請","answer":["ようせい"]},
    {"meaning":"training, development","question":"養成","answer":["ようせい"]},
    {"meaning":"leisure, leisure time, spare time","question":"余暇","answer":["よか"]},
    {"meaning":"side show, entertainment","question":"余興","answer":["よきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"deposit, bank account","question":"預金","answer":["よきん"]},
    {"meaning":"check, restraint, oppression, suppression","question":"抑圧","answer":["よくあつ"]},
    {"meaning":"bathroom, bath","question":"浴室","answer":["よくしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"suppression","question":"抑制","answer":["よくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"sumo grand champion","question":"横綱","answer":["よこづな"]},
    {"meaning":"good or bad, merits or demerits, quality, suitability","question":"善し悪し","answer":["よしあし"]},
    {"meaning":"government party, (ruling) party in power, government","question":"与党","answer":["よとう"]},
    {"meaning":"to abate, to weaken, to be emaciated, to be dejected, to be perplexed","question":"弱まる","answer":["よわまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to weaken","question":"弱める","answer":["よわめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to weaken, to be troubled, to be downcast, to be emaciated, to be dejected, to be perplexed, to impair","question":"弱る","answer":["よわる"]},
    {"meaning":"dairy (farm)","question":"酪農","answer":["らくのう"]},
    {"meaning":"abuse, misuse, misappropriation, using to excess","question":"濫用","answer":["らんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"theory, reason","question":"理屈","answer":["りくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"intelligence","question":"利根","answer":["りこん"]},
    {"meaning":"profit, returns","question":"利潤","answer":["りじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"abbreviation, acronym","question":"略語","answer":["りゃくご"]},
    {"meaning":"pillage, plunder, looting, robbery","question":"略奪","answer":["りゃくだつ"]},
    {"question":"言伝","answer":["ことづて"],"meaning":"(oral) message; declaration; hearsay; rumour; rumor"},
    {"meaning":"area, domain, territory, field, region, regime","question":"領域","answer":["りょういき"]},
    {"meaning":"comprehension, consent, understanding, roger (on the radio)","question":"了解","answer":["りょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"territorial waters","question":"領海","answer":["りょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"both extremities, north and south poles, positive and negative poles","question":"両極","answer":["りょうきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"acknowledgement, understanding (e.g. please be understanding of the mess during our renovation)","question":"了承","answer":["りょうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"territory, dominion","question":"領地","answer":["りょうち"]},
    {"meaning":"dominion, territory, possession","question":"領土","answer":["りょうど"]},
    {"meaning":"passport","question":"旅券","answer":["りょけん"]},
    {"meaning":"personal history, background, career, log","question":"履歴","answer":["りれき"]},
    {"question":"親しむ","answer":["したしむ"],"meaning":"to be intimate with; to befriend"},
    {"meaning":"forestry","question":"林業","answer":["りんぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"analogy","question":"類推","answer":["るいすい"]},
    {"meaning":"cruelty, coldheartedness, relentless, ruthless","question":"冷酷","answer":["れいこく"]},
    {"meaning":"cold storage, refrigeration","question":"冷蔵","answer":["れいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"coolness, indifference","question":"冷淡","answer":["れいたん"]},
    {"meaning":"love, love-making, passion, emotion, affections","question":"恋愛","answer":["れんあい"]},
    {"meaning":"solidarity","question":"連帯","answer":["れんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"commonwealth, federation of states","question":"連邦","answer":["れんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"league, union, alliance","question":"連盟","answer":["れんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"senility, senile decay","question":"老衰","answer":["ろうすい"]},
    {"meaning":"reading aloud, recitation","question":"朗読","answer":["ろうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"waste, extravagance","question":"浪費","answer":["ろうひ"]},
    {"meaning":"1. frank, blunt, plain, outspoken, 2. conspicuous, open, 3. broad, suggestive","question":"露骨","answer":["ろこつ"]},
    {"meaning":"selfishness, egoism, wilfulness, disobedience, whim","question":"我がまま","answer":["わがまま"]},
    {"meaning":"frame, slide","question":"枠","answer":["わく"]},
    {"meaning":"planet","question":"惑星","answer":["わくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"art, technique","question":"技","answer":["わざ"]},
    {"meaning":"troublesome, annoying, complicated","question":"煩わしい","answer":["わずらわしい"]},
    {"meaning":"division (math)","question":"割り算","answer":["わりざん"]},
    {"question":"見逃す","answer":["みのがす"],"meaning":"to miss; to overlook; to fail to notice, to turn a blind eye (to a wrongdoing etc.); to ignore, to pass up (an opportunity etc.)"},
    {"meaning":"to fan, to flap","question":"扇ぐ","answer":["あおぐ"]},
    {"question":"見苦しい","answer":["みぐるしい"],"meaning":"unsightly; ugly"},
    {"question":"見晴らし","answer":["みはらし"],"meaning":"view; prospect; outlook"},
    {"question":"西日","answer":["にしび"],"meaning":"westering sun; setting sun, Spanish-Japanese (gen. for translations and dictionaries)"},
    {"question":"裾","answer":["すそ"],"meaning":"hem; (trouser) cuff; shirttail, bottom edge, foot (of a mountain), tips (of hair), downstream"},
    {"question":"蜂蜜","answer":["はちみつ"],"meaning":"honey"},
    {"meaning":"compression, condensation, pressure","question":"圧縮","answer":["あっしゅく"]},
    {"question":"蓋","answer":["ふた"],"meaning":"cover; lid; cap"},
    {"question":"落ち葉","answer":["おちば"],"meaning":"fallen leaves; leaf litter, deciduous"},
    {"meaning":"unexpectedly","question":"案外","answer":["あんがい"]},
    {"question":"萎える","answer":["なえる"],"meaning":"to lose strength; to become weak; to waste away, to wither; to droop"},
    {"question":"苛める","answer":["いじめる"],"meaning":"to tease; to torment; to persecute; to chastise"},
    {"question":"良質","answer":["りょうしつ"],"meaning":"good quality; fine quality; superior quality; high quality"},
    {"meaning":"once, for a moment, one morning, temporarily","question":"一旦","answer":["いったん"]},
    {"meaning":"water well","question":"井戸","answer":["いど"]},
    {"question":"良識","answer":["りょうしき"],"meaning":"good sense"},
    {"meaning":"to be proud, to swagger","question":"威張る","answer":["いばる"]},
    {"question":"船乗り","answer":["ふなのり"],"meaning":"getting on board, sailor; seaman"},
    {"meaning":"to starve","question":"飢える","answer":["うえる"]},
    {"question":"舟運","answer":["しゅううん"],"meaning":"transportation by water (e.g. by ship)"},
    {"question":"自ら","answer":["みずから","おのずから"],"meaning":"naturally; as a matter of course, oneself, for one's self; personally"},
    {"question":"臆病","answer":["おくびょう"],"meaning":"cowardice; timidity"},
    {"meaning":"party, banquet","question":"宴会","answer":["えんかい"]},
    {"question":"腫れる","answer":["はれる"],"meaning":"to swell (from inflammation); to become swollen"},
    {"question":"背く","answer":["そむく"],"meaning":"to run counter to; to go against; to disobey; to infringe"},
    {"question":"股","answer":["もも","また"],"meaning":"crotch; crutch; groin; thigh, fork (in a tree, road, river, etc.); tines (of a fork), thigh, femoral"},
    {"question":"考古学","answer":["こうこがく"],"meaning":"archaeology; archeology"},
    {"question":"老ける","answer":["ふける"],"meaning":"to age; to grow old (esp. in appearance); to show marks of age"},
    {"question":"老いる","answer":["おいる"],"meaning":"to age; to grow old"},
    {"question":"羽音","answer":["はおと"],"meaning":"sound of flapping wings (of a bird), buzz; hum (of an insect)"},
    {"question":"羽毛","answer":["うもう"],"meaning":"feathers; plumage; down"},
    {"meaning":"to neglect, to be off guard, to be feeling better","question":"怠る","answer":["おこたる"]},
    {"question":"罵る","answer":["ののしる"],"meaning":"to abuse (verbally); to curse at; to shout abuse at; to speak ill of"},
    {"question":"縁","answer":["えん","ゆかり","ふち","へり","えにし"],"meaning":"related to (some person or place); affinity; connection, fate; destiny (esp. as a mysterious force that binds two people together), relationship (e.g. between two people); bond; link; connection, family ties; affinity, opportunity; chance (to meet someone and start a relationship), pratyaya (indirect conditions, as opposed to direct causes), narrow open-air veranda, rim; brim; edge; brink, reason; significance; cause, something to rely on; aid; clue; way; means, someone to rely on; relative, reminder; memento, edge (of a river, woods, etc.); shoulder (of a road), rim; brim; hem; margin; fringe; selvage, fabric border (of a tatami mat, etc.); edging"},
    {"question":"綻びる","answer":["ほころびる"],"meaning":"to come apart at the seams; to be ripped; to be torn, to begin to open; to begin to bloom, to smile broadly; to break into a smile"},
    {"question":"絶つ","answer":["たつ"],"meaning":"to sever; to cut off, to suppress; to eradicate; to exterminate, to abstain (from); to give up"},
    {"question":"絶える","answer":["たえる"],"meaning":"to die out; to peter out; to become extinct, to cease; to be stopped; to be discontinued; to be cut off"},
    {"meaning":"to sell wholesale, grated (vegetables)","question":"卸す","answer":["おろす"]},
    {"meaning":"grace, favor, blessing, benefit","question":"恩恵","answer":["おんけい"]},
    {"question":"給食","answer":["きゅうしょく"],"meaning":"provision of lunch (e.g. at office, school, etc.); providing a meal; lunch service"},
    {"meaning":"intro, outline, general remarks","question":"概論","answer":["がいろん"]},
    {"question":"給仕","answer":["きゅうじ"],"meaning":"waiting on a table; serving (at dinner), waiter; waitress; waitperson; server; cabin boy; bellboy; page; pageboy, office boy; office girl"},
    {"meaning":"hedge","question":"垣根","answer":["かきね"]},
    {"question":"経る","answer":["へる"],"meaning":"to pass; to elapse; to go by, to pass through; to go through, to experience; to go through; to undergo"},
    {"meaning":"expansion","question":"拡充","answer":["かくじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"expansion, extension, enlargement, escape (ESC)","question":"拡張","answer":["かくちょう"]},
    {"question":"粗筋","answer":["あらすじ"],"meaning":"outline; summary; argument"},
    {"question":"節","answer":["せつ","ふし"],"meaning":"occasion; time, section (of a literary work); paragraph; verse; stanza; passage, principle; integrity, node (of a plant stem), clause, (taxonomical) section, knot (nautical mile per hour), joint; knuckle, tune; melody, knot (in wood); node in a bamboo stem, part; notable characteristic, characteristic way of speaking, space between two nodes (on bamboo, etc.)"},
    {"question":"空ろ","answer":["うつろ"],"meaning":"cavity; hollow; void, hollow (voice); empty (heart); blank (eyes, face, etc.); vacant (stare)"},
    {"meaning":"katakana","question":"片仮名","answer":["かたかな"]},
    {"meaning":"lump, mass, clod, cluster","question":"塊","answer":["かたまり"]},
    {"question":"空しい","answer":["むなしい"],"meaning":"empty; void; vacant, vain; fruitless; futile; ineffective, lifeless"},
    {"question":"種々","answer":["くさぐさ"],"meaning":"variety"},
    {"meaning":"parenthesis, brackets","question":"括弧","answer":["かっこ"]},
    {"question":"碑石","answer":["ひせき"],"meaning":"stone monument"},
    {"question":"破廉恥","answer":["はれんち"],"meaning":"shameless; infamous; disgraceful"},
    {"question":"研ぐ","answer":["とぐ"],"meaning":"to sharpen; to hone; to whet; to grind, to wash (rice), to scour; to polish; to burnish"},
    {"question":"知恵","answer":["ちえ"],"meaning":"wisdom; wit; sagacity; sense; intelligence, prajna (insight leading to enlightenment)"},
    {"question":"真心","answer":["まごころ"],"meaning":"sincerity; devotion"},
    {"question":"真下","answer":["ました"],"meaning":"right under; directly below"},
    {"meaning":"song, ballad","question":"歌謡","answer":["かよう"]},
    {"meaning":"shell, husk, hull, chaff","question":"殻","answer":["から"]},
    {"question":"真上","answer":["まうえ"],"meaning":"just above; right overhead"},
    {"meaning":"money order, exchange","question":"為替","answer":["かわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"space, interval, SPC","question":"間隔","answer":["かんかく"]},
    {"question":"真に","answer":["まことに"],"meaning":"indeed; really; absolutely; truly; actually; very; quite"},
    {"question":"省略","answer":["しょうりゃく"],"meaning":"omission; abbreviation; abridgment; abridgement"},
    {"question":"相応しい","answer":["ふさわしい"],"meaning":"appropriate; adequate; suitable; fitting; worthy"},
    {"question":"直ぐ","answer":["すぐ"],"meaning":"immediately; at once; directly, soon; before long; shortly, easily; readily; without difficulty, right (near); nearby; just (handy), honest; upright; frank; straightforward"},
    {"question":"目論見","answer":["もくろみ"],"meaning":"plan; scheme; project; program; programme; intention; goal"},
    {"meaning":"instrument","question":"器械","answer":["きかい"]},
    {"question":"目蓋","answer":["まぶた"],"meaning":"eyelid; eyelids"},
    {"question":"目盛","answer":["めもり"],"meaning":"scale; gradations"},
    {"question":"発作","answer":["ほっさ"],"meaning":"fit; spasm; attack; seizure"},
    {"meaning":"foundation, basis","question":"基礎","answer":["きそ"]},
    {"question":"病む","answer":["やむ"],"meaning":"to fall ill; to suffer from; to have something wrong with"},
    {"question":"病","answer":["やまい"],"meaning":"illness; disease, bad habit; weakness; fault, pain; trouble, illness, disease; -pathy"},
    {"meaning":"rest, break, recreation","question":"休養","answer":["きゅうよう"]},
    {"question":"疾病","answer":["しっぺい"],"meaning":"illness; disease"},
    {"meaning":"culture, education, refinement, cultivation","question":"教養","answer":["きょうよう"]},
    {"question":"疎か","answer":["おろそか"],"meaning":"negligent; neglectful; careless; remiss, not to mention ...; needless to say ...; not to speak of ...; not only ..., negligent; neglectful; careless; remiss"},
    {"question":"畳","answer":["たたみ","じょう"],"meaning":"counter for tatami mats, measure of room size (in mat units), tatami mat; Japanese straw floor coverings, folding paper-case; kimono wrapping paper"},
    {"meaning":"to break, to smash","question":"砕く","answer":["くだく"]},
    {"meaning":"to break, to be broken","question":"砕ける","answer":["くだける"]},
    {"meaning":"lips","question":"唇","answer":["くちびる"]},
    {"question":"画期","answer":["かっき"],"meaning":"transition from one epoch to another; change of era"},
    {"meaning":"to serve sake","question":"酌む","answer":["くむ"]},
    {"question":"甲乙","answer":["こうおつ"],"meaning":"A and B; excellent and good; similarity, discrimination; discernment; distinction, first and second parties (in legal contexts)"},
    {"question":"田園","answer":["でんえん"],"meaning":"the country; countryside; rural districts, cultivated land; fields"},
    {"meaning":"country, district","question":"郡","answer":["ぐん"]},
    {"meaning":"fluorescent lamp, person who is slow to react","question":"蛍光灯","answer":["けいこうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"continuation","question":"継続","answer":["けいぞく"]},
    {"question":"産婦人科","answer":["さんふじんか"],"meaning":"maternity and gynaecology department (gynecology); department of obstetrics and gynaecology (gynecology)"},
    {"question":"生真面目","answer":["きまじめ"],"meaning":"too serious; person who is too serious; honesty; sincerity"},
    {"question":"生やす","answer":["はやす"],"meaning":"to grow; to cultivate; to wear a beard"},
    {"question":"生かす","answer":["いかす"],"meaning":"to make (the best) use of; to leverage (skills, attributes, experience, etc.); to capitalise on (experience, etc), to let live; to keep alive, to revive; to resuscitate"},
    {"meaning":"geta (Japanese footwear), wooden clogs","question":"下駄","answer":["げた"]},
    {"meaning":"masterpiece, best work, boner, blunder","question":"傑作","answer":["けっさく"]},
    {"meaning":"modesty, humility","question":"謙虚","answer":["けんきょ"]},
    {"question":"甚だ","answer":["はなはだ"],"meaning":"very; greatly; exceedingly"},
    {"question":"玩具","answer":["がんぐ","おもちゃ"],"meaning":"toy; plaything"},
    {"meaning":"strict, rigour, severe, firm","question":"厳重","answer":["げんじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"microscope","question":"顕微鏡","answer":["けんびきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"Go (board game of capturing territory)","question":"碁","answer":["ご"]},
    {"meaning":"to ask, to request","question":"請う","answer":["こう"]},
    {"meaning":"high class, high grade","question":"高級","answer":["こうきゅう"]},
    {"question":"狙撃","answer":["そげき"],"meaning":"shooting; sniping"},
    {"meaning":"the public","question":"公衆","answer":["こうしゅう"]},
    {"question":"犯す","answer":["おかす"],"meaning":"to commit (e.g. crime); to perpetrate; to make (e.g. mistake), to break (e.g. rule); to violate; to transgress; to contravene, to rape; to violate; to ravish; to deflower"},
    {"question":"犬死に","answer":["いぬじに"],"meaning":"dying in vain; wasteful sacrifice of life"},
    {"meaning":"item","question":"項目","answer":["こうもく"]},
    {"question":"物体ない","answer":["もったいない"],"meaning":"impious; profane; sacrilegious, too good; more than one deserves; unworthy of, wasteful"},
    {"question":"父母","answer":["ふぼ","ちちはは"],"meaning":"father and mother; parents"},
    {"meaning":"personal expenses, pocket money, spending money, incidental expenses, allowance","question":"小遣い","answer":["こづかい"]},
    {"question":"煙たい","answer":["けむたい"],"meaning":"smoky, awkward; ill at ease"},
    {"meaning":"Koto (Japanese harp)","question":"琴","answer":["こと"]},
    {"meaning":"speech, expression, wording","question":"言葉遣い","answer":["ことばづかい"]},
    {"question":"無駄遣い","answer":["むだづかい"],"meaning":"wasting ... on (e.g. money); squandering; waste; frittering away"},
    {"question":"無難","answer":["ぶなん"],"meaning":"safe; secure, acceptable; passable; faultless; innocuous"},
    {"question":"無闇に","answer":["むやみに"],"meaning":"thoughtlessly; recklessly; rashly; indiscriminately; indiscreetly; at random, excessively; unreasonably; immoderately; absurdly"},
    {"meaning":"navy blue, deep blue","question":"紺","answer":["こん"]},
    {"meaning":"menu, program, schedule","question":"献立","answer":["こんだて"]},
    {"meaning":"request, demand, claim, urge (action), press for","question":"催促","answer":["さいそく"]},
    {"question":"無邪気","answer":["むじゃき"],"meaning":"innocence; simple-mindedness"},
    {"meaning":"sewing","question":"裁縫","answer":["さいほう"]},
    {"question":"無言","answer":["むごん"],"meaning":"silence"},
    {"question":"無礼","answer":["ぶれい"],"meaning":"impolite; rude"},
    {"question":"無下に","answer":["むげに"],"meaning":"bluntly (refusing, etc.); flatly; out of hand; completely"},
    {"meaning":"manufacture","question":"作製","answer":["さくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"tatami room","question":"座敷","answer":["ざしき"]},
    {"question":"為来り","answer":["しきたり"],"meaning":"custom; convention; tradition; mores; conventional practice"},
    {"meaning":"to shine, to strike","question":"射す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"question":"為さる","answer":["なさる"],"meaning":"to do"},
    {"meaning":"to disturb, to prevent","question":"妨げる","answer":["さまたげる"]},
    {"question":"滴","answer":["しずく"],"meaning":"drop (of water); drip, dripping; drop, counter for drops of liquid"},
    {"meaning":"acidity","question":"酸性","answer":["さんせい"]},
    {"question":"滲む","answer":["にじむ"],"meaning":"to run (of liquid); to spread, to blur; to blot; to be blurred, to ooze; to well up (of tears, etc.), to show through (of feelings, emotions, etc.); to reveal itself"},
    {"question":"滑稽","answer":["こっけい"],"meaning":"funny; humorous; humourous; comical; laughable; ridiculous; joking"},
    {"meaning":"site","question":"敷地","answer":["しきち"]},
    {"question":"溺死","answer":["できし"],"meaning":"death by drowning"},
    {"meaning":"to spread out, to lay out","question":"敷く","answer":["しく"]},
    {"meaning":"to grow thick, to luxuriate, to be luxurious","question":"茂る","answer":["しげる"]},
    {"meaning":"magnet","question":"磁石","answer":["じしゃく"]},
    {"question":"渡り鳥","answer":["わたりどり"],"meaning":"migratory bird; bird of passage"},
    {"meaning":"writing","question":"執筆","answer":["しっぴつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to tie, to bind","question":"縛る","answer":["しばる"]},
    {"question":"海抜","answer":["かいばつ"],"meaning":"height above sea level"},
    {"meaning":"paper money, notes, bills","question":"紙幣","answer":["しへい"]},
    {"meaning":"to press, to wring, to squeeze","question":"絞る","answer":["しぼる"]},
    {"meaning":"full name, identity","question":"氏名","answer":["しめい"]},
    {"meaning":"closing, cut-off, end, deadline, Closed, No Entrance","question":"締切","answer":["しめきり"]},
    {"meaning":"to shut up","question":"締め切る","answer":["しめきる"]},
    {"meaning":"faucet, tap","question":"蛇口","answer":["じゃぐち"]},
    {"question":"浮気","answer":["うわき"],"meaning":"extramarital sex; affair; fooling around, infidelity; wantonness; unfaithfulness; inconstancy; fickleness; caprice"},
    {"meaning":"repair, mending","question":"修繕","answer":["しゅうぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"inauguration, assumption of office","question":"就任","answer":["しゅうにん"]},
    {"question":"浮力","answer":["ふりょく"],"meaning":"buoyancy; floating power"},
    {"question":"浅瀬","answer":["あさせ"],"meaning":"shoal; shallows; sand bar; ford"},
    {"meaning":"official tour, business trip","question":"出張","answer":["しゅっちょう"]},
    {"question":"活かす","answer":["いかす"],"meaning":"to make (the best) use of; to leverage (skills, attributes, experience, etc.); to capitalise on (experience, etc), to let live; to keep alive, to revive; to resuscitate"},
    {"meaning":"circulation, rotation, cycle","question":"循環","answer":["じゅんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"police, policeman","question":"巡査","answer":["じゅんさ"]},
    {"meaning":"order, sequence, procedure","question":"順序","answer":["じゅんじょ"]},
    {"question":"油井","answer":["ゆせい"],"meaning":"oil well"},
    {"meaning":"Japanese chess","question":"将棋","answer":["しょうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"advanced level, high grade, senior","question":"上級","answer":["じょうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"paper sliding door","question":"障子","answer":["しょうじ"]},
    {"question":"氾濫","answer":["はんらん"],"meaning":"overflowing; flood; inundation; deluge, oversupply; plethora"},
    {"question":"水田","answer":["すいでん"],"meaning":"(water-filled) paddy field"},
    {"meaning":"elementary level","question":"初級","answer":["しょきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"assistant professor","question":"助教授","answer":["じょきょうじゅ"]},
    {"question":"気風","answer":["きふう"],"meaning":"character; traits; ethos, character; disposition; spirit; temperament"},
    {"meaning":"tableware","question":"食器","answer":["しょっき"]},
    {"question":"気立て","answer":["きだて"],"meaning":"disposition; nature"},
    {"meaning":"amateur, novice","question":"素人","answer":["しろうと"]},
    {"meaning":"bullet train (very high speed), shinkansen","question":"新幹線","answer":["しんかんせん"]},
    {"question":"気泡","answer":["きほう"],"meaning":"(air) bubble (esp. in a liquid)"},
    {"question":"民主","answer":["みんしゅ"],"meaning":"democracy; popular sovereignty, democratic"},
    {"question":"母校","answer":["ぼこう"],"meaning":"alma mater"},
    {"question":"殺生","answer":["せっしょう"],"meaning":"killing; destruction of life, barbarous; callous; brutal; cruel"},
    {"meaning":"cooking, culinary arts","question":"炊事","answer":["すいじ"]},
    {"question":"残高","answer":["ざんだか"],"meaning":"(bank) balance; remainder"},
    {"meaning":"vertical, perpendicular","question":"垂直","answer":["すいちょく"]},
    {"question":"歩む","answer":["あゆむ"],"meaning":"to walk; to go on foot"},
    {"meaning":"essays, miscellaneous writings","question":"随筆","answer":["ずいひつ"]},
    {"meaning":"picture book","question":"図鑑","answer":["ずかん"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese cedar","question":"杉","answer":["すぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"likes and dislikes, taste","question":"好き嫌い","answer":["すききらい"]},
    {"question":"正弦","answer":["せいげん"],"meaning":"sine"},
    {"question":"正に","answer":["まさに"],"meaning":"exactly; surely; certainly, right then; just then; at that moment, just (about to); on the verge (of doing or happening), duly; naturally"},
    {"meaning":"","question":"棄てる","answer":["すてる"]},
    {"question":"欠く","answer":["かく"],"meaning":"to chip; to nick; to break; to crack, to lack"},
    {"meaning":"ink","question":"墨","answer":["すみ"]},
    {"question":"様相","answer":["ようそう"],"meaning":"aspect; phase; condition, modality (philosophy)"},
    {"meaning":"sumo wrestling","question":"相撲","answer":["すもう"]},
    {"meaning":"measurement, size, dimension","question":"寸法","answer":["すんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"manufacture, production","question":"製作","answer":["せいさく"]},
    {"question":"楽観","answer":["らっかん"],"meaning":"optimism"},
    {"question":"業腹","answer":["ごうはら"],"meaning":"spite; resentment"},
    {"question":"梅干","answer":["うめぼし"],"meaning":"umeboshi; pickled ume; pickled plum"},
    {"meaning":"earthenware, crockery, china","question":"瀬戸物","answer":["せともの"]},
    {"question":"柵","answer":["さく","しがらみ"],"meaning":"fence; paling; railing, weir, bonds; fetters; ties of obligation, fortress (surrounded by a wall, moat, etc.)"},
    {"question":"柳眉","answer":["りゅうび"],"meaning":"beautiful eyebrows"},
    {"meaning":"stopper, cork, stopcock","question":"栓","answer":["せん"]},
    {"question":"柔和","answer":["にゅうわ"],"meaning":"gentle; mild; meek; tender"},
    {"meaning":"folding fan","question":"扇子","answer":["せんす"]},
    {"question":"果たして","answer":["はたして"],"meaning":"as was expected; just as one thought; sure enough; as a result, really? (in questions); ever?"},
    {"meaning":"propaganda, publicity","question":"宣伝","answer":["せんでん"]},
    {"meaning":"electric fan","question":"扇風機","answer":["せんぷうき"]},
    {"meaning":"storehouse, warehouse, godown","question":"倉庫","answer":["そうこ"]},
    {"meaning":"production, literary creation, work","question":"創作","answer":["そうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"funeral","question":"葬式","answer":["そうしき"]},
    {"question":"束の間","answer":["つかのま"],"meaning":"moment; brief time; brief; transient"},
    {"meaning":"zoori (Japanese footwear), sandals","question":"草履","answer":["ぞうり"]},
    {"meaning":"to belong to, to come under, to be affiliated with, to be subject to","question":"属する","answer":["ぞくする"]},
    {"question":"本音","answer":["ほんね"],"meaning":"real intention; motive; true opinion; what one really thinks"},
    {"meaning":"to stray (turn) from subject, to get lost, to go astray","question":"逸れる","answer":["それる"]},
    {"meaning":"abacus","question":"算盤","answer":["そろばん"]},
    {"question":"本名","answer":["ほんみょう"],"meaning":"real name"},
    {"meaning":"drum, tambourine","question":"太鼓","answer":["たいこ"]},
    {"question":"未婚","answer":["みこん"],"meaning":"unmarried"},
    {"question":"未だ","answer":["いまだ","まだ"],"meaning":"as yet; hitherto; only; still, not yet (with negative verb), more; besides, unfinished; incomplete; not yet finished with"},
    {"question":"木綿","answer":["もめん"],"meaning":"cotton (material), red silk-cotton tree (Bombax ceiba), string made of cut steamed, soaked mulberry bark fibers"},
    {"question":"朝寝坊","answer":["あさねぼう"],"meaning":"oversleeping; late riser"},
    {"meaning":"to store, to lay in stock","question":"蓄える","answer":["たくわえる"]},
    {"meaning":"free of charge, mere, sole, only, usual, common","question":"只","answer":["ただ"]},
    {"meaning":"but, however, provided that","question":"但し","answer":["ただし"]},
    {"question":"有難う","answer":["ありがとう"],"meaning":"Thank you; Thanks"},
    {"meaning":"valid, proper, right, appropriate","question":"妥当","answer":["だとう"]},
    {"meaning":"fresh water","question":"淡水","answer":["たんすい"]},
    {"meaning":"to swear, to vow, to take an oath, to pledge","question":"誓う","answer":["ちかう"]},
    {"question":"有様","answer":["ありさま"],"meaning":"state; condition; circumstances; the way things are or should be; truth"},
    {"question":"最早","answer":["もはや"],"meaning":"already; now, no longer; not any more"},
    {"question":"曲","answer":["きょく"],"meaning":"song; tune; composition; piece of music, corner; nook; recess, a shadow; a shade, wickedness; evil; calamity; disaster, long segment of a noh play forming its musical highlight, wrong; improper; indecent"},
    {"question":"暗殺","answer":["あんさつ"],"meaning":"assassination"},
    {"meaning":"abstract","question":"抽象","answer":["ちゅうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"carving, engraving, sculpture","question":"彫刻","answer":["ちょうこく"]},
    {"question":"暖房","answer":["だんぼう"],"meaning":"(indoor) heating"},
    {"question":"時折","answer":["ときおり"],"meaning":"sometimes"},
    {"question":"映える","answer":["はえる"],"meaning":"to shine; to look attractive; to look pretty"},
    {"question":"明々後日","answer":["しあさって","みょうみょうごにち"],"meaning":"in three days' time; two days after tomorrow"},
    {"meaning":"interpretation","question":"通訳","answer":["つうやく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dip in, to soak","question":"浸ける","answer":["つける"]},
    {"meaning":"rope","question":"綱","answer":["つな"]},
    {"question":"早急","answer":["さっきゅう","そうきゅう"],"meaning":"immediate; prompt; quick; rapid; urgent; pressing"},
    {"question":"日向","answer":["ひなた"],"meaning":"sunny place; in the sun"},
    {"meaning":"unevenness, roughness, ruggedness","question":"凸凹","answer":["でこぼこ"]},
    {"meaning":"notebook","question":"手帳","answer":["てちょう"]},
    {"question":"斑","answer":["ハン","まだら","むら","ぶち","ふ"],"meaning":"uneven; irregular; speckled; mottled, erratic; inconsistent, fickle; capricious; fitful, spots; speckles; mottles, spots; speckles; mottles, speckled; spotted"},
    {"question":"敢えて","answer":["あえて"],"meaning":"purposely (of something needless, unexpected or seemingly counterproductive, etc.); daringly (doing something); deliberately; intentionally, not necessarily; not particularly; not especially, definitely not"},
    {"meaning":"contagion","question":"伝染","answer":["でんせん"]},
    {"question":"放り出す","answer":["ほうりだす"],"meaning":"to throw out, to drop; to toss; to dump, to abandon; to neglect; to leave behind; to give up, to dismiss; to fire; to expel, to expel; to eject; to push out; to force out"},
    {"meaning":"ridge, (mountain) pass, difficult part","question":"峠","answer":["とうげ"]},
    {"meaning":"scattering, a scatter, dispersion","question":"統計","answer":["とうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"transparency, cleanness","question":"透明","answer":["とうめい"]},
    {"question":"改宗","answer":["かいしゅう"],"meaning":"religious conversion"},
    {"meaning":"cupboard, locker, closet, wardrobe","question":"戸棚","answer":["とだな"]},
    {"question":"摂取","answer":["せっしゅ"],"meaning":"intake; absorption; adoption, assimilation"},
    {"question":"搾取","answer":["さくしゅ"],"meaning":"exploitation; squeezing; sweating"},
    {"meaning":"to comfort, to console","question":"慰める","answer":["なぐさめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to accomplish, to do","question":"為す","answer":["なす"]},
    {"question":"揺れる","answer":["ゆれる"],"meaning":"to shake; to sway; to waver"},
    {"question":"推薦","answer":["すいせん"],"meaning":"recommendation; referral; endorsement"},
    {"question":"捕らえる","answer":["とらえる"],"meaning":"to catch; to capture; to seize; to arrest; to grab; to catch hold of, to grasp (e.g. meaning); to perceive; to capture (e.g. features), to captivate; to move (one's heart)"},
    {"meaning":"to become muddy, to get impure","question":"濁る","answer":["にごる"]},
    {"question":"指図","answer":["さしず"],"meaning":"instruction; mandate; directions"},
    {"meaning":"wife","question":"女房","answer":["にょうぼう"]},
    {"question":"持続","answer":["じぞく"],"meaning":"continuation; persisting; lasting; sustaining; enduring"},
    {"meaning":"to sew","question":"縫う","answer":["ぬう"]},
    {"question":"招き","answer":["まねき"],"meaning":"invitation"},
    {"question":"打開","answer":["だかい"],"meaning":"break in the deadlock"},
    {"question":"手際","answer":["てぎわ"],"meaning":"performance; skill; tact"},
    {"meaning":"haiku poetry","question":"俳句","answer":["はいく"]},
    {"question":"手配","answer":["てはい"],"meaning":"arrangement; preparations, search (by police)"},
    {"meaning":"","question":"斜","answer":["はす"]},
    {"meaning":"a bowl, a pot","question":"鉢","answer":["はち"]},
    {"meaning":"exhibition, demonstration, utilization, display","question":"発揮","answer":["はっき"]},
    {"question":"手近","answer":["てぢか"],"meaning":"near; close by; within reach; handy, familiar"},
    {"question":"手数","answer":["てすう","てかず"],"meaning":"trouble; bother, number of moves (in go, shogi, etc.), number of punches (in boxing)"},
    {"meaning":"extreme, excessive, terrible","question":"甚だしい","answer":["はなはだしい"]},
    {"meaning":"bride","question":"花嫁","answer":["はなよめ"]},
    {"question":"手掛かり","answer":["てがかり"],"meaning":"clue; lead; key; trail; scent; track, handhold; hold"},
    {"meaning":"to be in high spirits, to be full of vigor","question":"張り切る","answer":["はりきる"]},
    {"question":"戦","answer":["いくさ"],"meaning":"war; battle; campaign; fight, troops; forces, war; battle, match; competition"},
    {"question":"成る丈","answer":["なるたけ"],"meaning":"as much as possible; if possible"},
    {"meaning":"to turn over, to overturn, to knock over, to upset, to turn inside out","question":"引っ繰り返す","answer":["ひっくりかえす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be overturned, to be upset, to topple over, to be reversed","question":"引っ繰り返る","answer":["ひっくりかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"necessities, necessary article, requisite, essential","question":"必需品","answer":["ひつじゅひん"]},
    {"question":"成り立つ","answer":["なりたつ"],"meaning":"to consist of; to be made up of; to be composed of, to be practical (logical, feasible, viable); to be concluded; to hold true"},
    {"question":"懸想","answer":["けそう"],"meaning":"falling in love; attachment"},
    {"question":"憂鬱","answer":["ゆううつ"],"meaning":"depression; melancholy; dejection; gloom"},
    {"question":"慣用","answer":["かんよう"],"meaning":"common; customary"},
    {"question":"慣例","answer":["かんれい"],"meaning":"custom; precedent; of convention"},
    {"meaning":"standard, level","question":"標準","answer":["ひょうじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"example, specimen","question":"標本","answer":["ひょうほん"]},
    {"question":"慌ただしい","answer":["あわただしい"],"meaning":"busy; hurried; confused; flurried"},
    {"meaning":"hiragana, 47 syllables, the cursive syllabary","question":"平仮名","answer":["ひらがな"]},
    {"meaning":"diffusion, spread","question":"普及","answer":["ふきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to swell, to expand, to inflate, to bulge","question":"膨らます","answer":["ふくらます"]},
    {"meaning":"to expand, to swell (out), to get big, to become inflated","question":"膨らむ","answer":["ふくらむ"]},
    {"meaning":"unclean, dirty, filthy, impure","question":"不潔","answer":["ふけつ"]},
    {"question":"意趣返し","answer":["いしゅがえし"],"meaning":"revenge"},
    {"meaning":"attached, belonging, affiliated","question":"附属","answer":["ふぞく"]},
    {"question":"情け深い","answer":["なさけぶかい"],"meaning":"tender-hearted; compassionate; charitable; good-hearted"},
    {"question":"情け","answer":["なさけ"],"meaning":"pity; sympathy; compassion; mercy, affection"},
    {"meaning":"to increase, to add to, to augment","question":"殖やす","answer":["ふやす"]},
    {"meaning":", pronunciation key","question":"振り仮名","answer":["ふりがな"]},
    {"meaning":"to behave, to conduct oneself, to entertain (vt)","question":"振舞う","answer":["ふるまう"]},
    {"meaning":"wrapping cloth, cloth wrapper","question":"風呂敷","answer":["ふろしき"]},
    {"meaning":"eruption","question":"噴火","answer":["ふんか"]},
    {"meaning":"literature, books (reference)","question":"文献","answer":["ぶんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"water fountain","question":"噴水","answer":["ふんすい"]},
    {"question":"悲鳴","answer":["ひめい"],"meaning":"shriek; scream"},
    {"meaning":"context","question":"文脈","answer":["ぶんみゃく"]},
    {"question":"悪者","answer":["わるもの"],"meaning":"bad fellow; rascal; ruffian; scoundrel"},
    {"meaning":"common, commonplace, ordinary, mediocre","question":"平凡","answer":["へいぼん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be dented, to be indented, to yield to, to give, to sink, to collapse, to cave in, to be snubbed","question":"凹む","answer":["へこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be shut out","question":"隔てる","answer":["へだてる"]},
    {"meaning":"holiday house, villa","question":"別荘","answer":["べっそう"]},
    {"meaning":"telescope","question":"望遠鏡","answer":["ぼうえんきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"huge, bulky, enormous, extensive, swelling, expansion","question":"膨大","answer":["ぼうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"brightness, cheerfulness, melodious","question":"朗らか","answer":["ほがらか"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) farm (livestock), (2) pasture land, meadow, grazing land","question":"牧場","answer":["ぼくじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"stock-farming","question":"牧畜","answer":["ぼくちく"]},
    {"question":"悪化","answer":["あっか"],"meaning":"(suffer) deterioration; growing worse; aggravation; degeneration; corruption"},
    {"meaning":"moat, canal","question":"堀","answer":["ほり"]},
    {"question":"恥","answer":["はじ"],"meaning":"shame; embarrassment; disgrace"},
    {"meaning":"Lantern Festival, Festival of the Dead, tray","question":"盆","answer":["ぼん"]},
    {"meaning":"basin (e.g. between mountains)","question":"盆地","answer":["ぼんち"]},
    {"meaning":"to sow (seeds)","question":"蒔く","answer":["まく"]},
    {"question":"急かす","answer":["せかす"],"meaning":"to hurry; to urge on"},
    {"meaning":"or, otherwise","question":"又は","answer":["または"]},
    {"question":"怠い","answer":["だるい"],"meaning":"sluggish; languid; listless; heavy (heart, legs, etc.); dull, bothersome; tiresome"},
    {"meaning":"rare, seldom","question":"稀","answer":["まれ"]},
    {"meaning":"cape (on coast)","question":"岬","answer":["みさき"]},
    {"meaning":"ugly","question":"醜い","answer":["みにくい"]},
    {"question":"思惑","answer":["おもわく","しわく"],"meaning":"expectation; anticipation; prediction; forecast; calculations, purpose; intention; motive; ulterior motive, others' opinions of one, speculation, perceptive mental disturbances"},
    {"meaning":"folk song, popular song","question":"民謡","answer":["みんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"humid, sultry","question":"蒸し暑い","answer":["むしあつい"]},
    {"meaning":"contradiction, inconsistency","question":"矛盾","answer":["むじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"purple colour, violet","question":"紫","answer":["むらさき"]},
    {"meaning":"each, individual","question":"銘々","answer":["めいめい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be blessed with, to be rich in","question":"恵まれる","answer":["めぐまれる"]},
    {"question":"怒り","answer":["いかり"],"meaning":"anger; rage; fury; wrath; indignation"},
    {"question":"心得","answer":["こころえ"],"meaning":"knowledge; understanding, rules; regulations; guideline; directions, deputy; acting"},
    {"meaning":"bother to do, tiresome","question":"面倒臭い","answer":["めんどうくさい"]},
    {"question":"後退","answer":["こうたい"],"meaning":"retreat, backspace; BS"},
    {"meaning":"event, festivities, function","question":"催し","answer":["もよおし"]},
    {"question":"待ち遠しい","answer":["まちどおしい"],"meaning":"looking forward to; anxiously awaited"},
    {"meaning":"directing arrow","question":"矢印","answer":["やじるし"]},
    {"meaning":"quiet, calm, leisurely","question":"悠々","answer":["ゆうゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"loose, lenient, slow","question":"緩い","answer":["ゆるい"]},
    {"question":"彼方","answer":["かなた","あなた","あちら","あっち"],"meaning":"beyond; across; the other side; the distance, that way (direction distant from both speaker and listener); over there; yonder, that one (something physically distant from both speaker and listener, or something not visible but known by both speaker and listener); that, that person (someone physically distant from both speaker and listener, or someone not present but known by both speaker and listener), there (place distant from both speaker and listener); over there; foreign country (esp. a Western nation)"},
    {"meaning":"gist, essentials, summary, fundamentals","question":"要旨","answer":["ようし"]},
    {"meaning":"infancy, childish, infantile","question":"幼稚","answer":["ようち"]},
    {"meaning":"kindergarten","question":"幼稚園","answer":["ようちえん"]},
    {"meaning":"wool","question":"羊毛","answer":["ようもう"]},
    {"meaning":"avarice, covetousness, greed","question":"欲張り","answer":["よくばり"]},
    {"question":"強いる","answer":["しいる"],"meaning":"to force; to compel; to coerce"},
    {"question":"強いて","answer":["しいて"],"meaning":"by force"},
    {"meaning":"column of text (e.g. as in a newspaper)","question":"欄","answer":["らん"]},
    {"question":"弄ぶ","answer":["もてあそぶ"],"meaning":"to play with (a toy, one's hair, etc.); to fiddle with, to toy with (one's emotions, etc.); to trifle with, to do with something as one pleases, to appreciate"},
    {"meaning":"temporary, special, extraordinary","question":"臨時","answer":["りんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to boil, to grow hot, to get excited, to gush forth","question":"湧く","answer":["わく"]},
    {"question":"丁寧","answer":["ていねい"],"meaning":"polite; courteous; civil, careful; close; thorough; conscientious"},
    {"question":"万人","answer":["ばんじん","ばんにん","まんにん"],"meaning":"all people; everybody, ten thousand people"},
    {"question":"万能","answer":["ばんのう"],"meaning":"all-purpose; utility, almighty; omnipotent"},
    {"question":"丈","answer":["たけ","じょう"],"meaning":"height; stature, length (esp. of clothing), all (one has); everything, magnificence (of a waka poem, etc.), 3.03 meters (ten shaku), length; measure, Mr.; Mrs."},
    {"question":"三日月","answer":["みかづき"],"meaning":"new moon; crescent moon"},
    {"question":"不可欠","answer":["ふかけつ"],"meaning":"indispensable; essential"},
    {"question":"不図","answer":["ふと"],"meaning":"suddenly; casually; accidentally; incidentally; unexpectedly; unintentionally"},
    {"question":"中程","answer":["なかほど"],"meaning":"(about) middle; midway"},
    {"question":"丹念","answer":["たんねん"],"meaning":"painstaking; careful; meticulous; scrupulous; detailed; elaborate"},
    {"question":"乙女","answer":["おとめ"],"meaning":"little girl; maiden; young lady; female usually between 7 and 18 years old"},
    {"question":"予め","answer":["あらかじめ"],"meaning":"beforehand; in advance; previously"},
    {"question":"交える","answer":["まじえる"],"meaning":"to mix; to combine, to exchange (words, fire, etc.), to cross (e.g. swords); to join together"},
    {"question":"交わる","answer":["まじわる"],"meaning":"to cross; to intersect; to join; to meet, to associate with; to mingle with; to consort with, to have a sexual relationship; to copulate"},
    {"question":"交互","answer":["こうご"],"meaning":"mutual; reciprocal; alternate"},
    {"question":"人柱","answer":["ひとばしら"],"meaning":"human pillar; human sacrifice"},
    {"question":"人質","answer":["ひとじち"],"meaning":"hostage"},
    {"question":"今更","answer":["いまさら"],"meaning":"now (after such a long time); at this late hour (i.e. it is too late for something); at this point of time, afresh; anew; again"},
    {"question":"仕える","answer":["つかえる"],"meaning":"to serve; to work for; to attend"},
    {"question":"仕様","answer":["しよう"],"meaning":"way; method; means; resource; remedy, (technical) specification"},
    {"question":"伝言","answer":["でんごん","つてごと"],"meaning":"verbal message; word, verbal message; word, rumour; rumor"},
    {"question":"似通う","answer":["にかよう"],"meaning":"to resemble closely"},
    {"question":"何処か","answer":["どこか"],"meaning":"somewhere; anywhere; in some respects"},
    {"question":"何故","answer":["なぜ","なにゆえ"],"meaning":"why; how"},
    {"question":"余弦","answer":["よげん"],"meaning":"cosine"},
    {"question":"余所見","answer":["よそみ"],"meaning":"looking away; looking aside"},
    {"question":"信者","answer":["しんじゃ"],"meaning":"believer; adherent; devotee"},
    {"question":"倣う","answer":["ならう"],"meaning":"to imitate; to follow; to emulate"},
    {"question":"値する","answer":["あたいする"],"meaning":"to be worth; to deserve; to merit"},
    {"question":"僅か","answer":["わずか"],"meaning":"only; merely; (a) little; small quantity"},
    {"question":"億万長者","answer":["おくまんちょうじゃ"],"meaning":"billionaire; multimillionaire; very rich person"},
    {"question":"優越","answer":["ゆうえつ"],"meaning":"supremacy; predominance; being superior to"},
    {"question":"元来","answer":["がんらい"],"meaning":"originally; primarily; essentially; logically; naturally"},
    {"question":"公","answer":["おおやけ"],"meaning":"you; buddy; pal, monarch; ruler; sovereign; (one's) master, public; open; formal; official; governmental, public matter; governmental matter, prince; duke, lord; sir, familiar or derogatory suffix"},
    {"question":"共鳴","answer":["きょうめい"],"meaning":"resonance; sympathetic (sound); (being in) sympathy"},
    {"question":"再び","answer":["ふたたび"],"meaning":"again; once more; a second time"},
    {"question":"冬眠","answer":["とうみん"],"meaning":"hibernation; winter sleep"},
    {"question":"凄い","answer":["すごい"],"meaning":"terrible; dreadful, amazing (e.g. of strength); great (e.g. of skills); wonderful; terrific, to a great extent; vast (in numbers)"},
    {"question":"分担","answer":["ぶんたん"],"meaning":"apportionment; allotment; share"},
    {"question":"初耳","answer":["はつみみ"],"meaning":"something heard for the first time; hearing something for the first time"},
    {"question":"初陣","answer":["ういじん"],"meaning":"first campaign; one's first battle"},
    {"question":"剥がす","answer":["はがす"],"meaning":"to tear off; to peel off; to rip off; to strip off; to skin; to flay; to disrobe; to deprive of; to detach; to disconnect"},
    {"question":"剥ぐ","answer":["はぐ"],"meaning":"to tear off; to peel off; to rip off; to strip off; to skin; to flay; to bark; to disrobe, to strip of (e.g. clothes, rank); to deprive of; to divest"},
    {"question":"勝る","answer":["まさる"],"meaning":"to excel; to surpass; to exceed; to have an edge; to be superior; to outrival, to outweigh; to preponderate"},
    {"question":"化ける","answer":["ばける"],"meaning":"to take the form of (esp. in ref. to a spirit, fox, raccoon dog, etc.); to assume the shape of; to turn oneself into; to transform oneself into, to disguise oneself as, to change radically; to metamorphose, to improve unexpectedly and dramatically (esp. of an actor, artist, rikishi, etc.), to age; to grow old (esp. in appearance); to show marks of age"},
    {"question":"危ぶむ","answer":["あやぶむ"],"meaning":"to fear; to have misgivings; to be doubtful; to mistrust"},
    {"question":"参議院","answer":["さんぎいん"],"meaning":"House of Councillors"},
    {"question":"受身","answer":["うけみ"],"meaning":"the defensive, passive attitude; passivity; passiveness, the passive; passive voice, ukemi (the art of falling safely)"},
    {"question":"可哀想","answer":["かわいそう"],"meaning":"poor; pitiable; pathetic; pitiful"},
    {"question":"可愛い","answer":["かわいい"],"meaning":"cute; adorable; charming; lovely; pretty, dear; precious; darling; pet, cute little; tiny"},
    {"question":"台無し","answer":["だいなし"],"meaning":"mess; spoiled; spoilt; (come to) nothing; ruin"},
    {"question":"同い年","answer":["おないどし"],"meaning":"the same age"},
    {"question":"同居","answer":["どうきょ"],"meaning":"coexistence; living together"},
    {"question":"名残","answer":["なごり"],"meaning":"remains; traces; vestiges; relics, (the sorrow of) parting, end"},
    {"question":"否決","answer":["ひけつ"],"meaning":"rejection; negation; voting down"},
    {"question":"告げる","answer":["つげる"],"meaning":"to tell; to inform; to announce, to indicate; to signal; to mark"},
    {"question":"和やか","answer":["なごやか"],"meaning":"mild; calm; gentle; quiet; harmonious"},
    {"question":"和らげる","answer":["やわらげる"],"meaning":"to soften; to moderate; to relieve"},
    {"question":"唐突","answer":["とうとつ"],"meaning":"abrupt; sudden"},
    {"question":"唾","answer":["つば","つばき"],"meaning":"saliva; spit; sputum"},
    {"question":"問屋","answer":["といや","とんや"],"meaning":"wholesale store"},
    {"question":"図々しい","answer":["ずうずうしい"],"meaning":"impudent; shameless"},
    {"question":"図る","answer":["はかる"],"meaning":"to plan; to attempt; to devise, to plot; to conspire; to scheme, to aim for; to strive for; to work towards; to seek"},
    {"question":"地主","answer":["じぬし"],"meaning":"landlord; landowner"},
    {"question":"地元","answer":["じもと"],"meaning":"home area; home town, local"},
    {"question":"基","answer":["もと","もとい"],"meaning":"origin; source, base; basis; foundation; root, cause, ingredient; material, original cost (or capital, principal, etc.), (plant) root; (tree) trunk, first section of a waka, handle (chopsticks, brush, etc.); grip, group, (free) radical, counter for installed or mounted objects (e.g. stone lanterns, gravestones, satellites), basis; foundation, cause"},
    {"question":"声高","answer":["こわだか"],"meaning":"with a loud voice"},
    {"question":"夕暮れ","answer":["ゆうぐれ"],"meaning":"evening; dusk; twilight"},
    {"question":"多岐","answer":["たき"],"meaning":"digression; many divergences"},
    {"question":"多忙","answer":["たぼう"],"meaning":"busy; pressure of work"},
    {"question":"夜具","answer":["やぐ"],"meaning":"bedding; bedclothes"},
    {"question":"夜更かし","answer":["よふかし"],"meaning":"staying up late; keeping late hours; sitting up late at night; nighthawk"},
    {"question":"大宗","answer":["たいそう"],"meaning":"leading figure; foundation"},
    {"question":"大尉","answer":["たいい"],"meaning":"captain (Army, U.S. Marine Corps, USAF); lieutenant (Navy); flight lieutenant (RAF, RAAF, RNZAF, etc.)"},
    {"question":"大空","answer":["おおぞら"],"meaning":"heavens; firmament; sky"},
    {"question":"奈落","answer":["ならく"],"meaning":"Naraka; hell; hades, very bottom; the end; worst possible circumstances, theatre basement; theater basement"},
    {"question":"好ましい","answer":["このましい"],"meaning":"nice; likeable; desirable"},
    {"question":"妬む","answer":["ねたむ"],"meaning":"to be jealous of; to envy; to begrudge"},
    {"question":"建前","answer":["たてまえ"],"meaning":"face; official stance; public position or attitude (as opposed to private thoughts), ceremony for the erection of the framework of a house"},
    {"question":"嫉妬","answer":["しっと"],"meaning":"jealousy; envy"},
    {"question":"完璧","answer":["かんぺき"],"meaning":"perfect; complete; flawless"},
    {"question":"定まる","answer":["さだまる"],"meaning":"to become settled; to be fixed"},
    {"question":"定める","answer":["さだめる"],"meaning":"to decide; to establish; to determine"},
    {"question":"宛","answer":["あて"],"meaning":"aim; object; purpose; end, expectations; prospects; hopes, something that can be relied upon, snack served with alcoholic drink, pad; guard, blow; strike, addressed to, per"},
    {"question":"宛てる","answer":["あてる"],"meaning":"to address"},
    {"question":"家主","answer":["やぬし","いえぬし"],"meaning":"landlord; landlady, house owner; home owner; head of the household"},
    {"question":"家来","answer":["けらい"],"meaning":"retainer; retinue; servant"},
    {"question":"容易い","answer":["たやすい"],"meaning":"easy; simple; light"},
    {"question":"寄与","answer":["きよ"],"meaning":"contribution; service"},
    {"question":"富","answer":["とみ"],"meaning":"riches; wealth; fortune, resources, lottery"},
    {"question":"富む","answer":["とむ"],"meaning":"to be rich; to become rich; to be abundant (with); to abound (with); to be rich (in)"},
    {"question":"尊ぶ","answer":["とうとぶ","たっとぶ"],"meaning":"to value; to prize; to esteem; to respect"},
    {"question":"小売","answer":["こうり"],"meaning":"retail"},
    {"question":"尚更","answer":["なおさら"],"meaning":"still more; even more; all the more, still less; even less"},
    {"question":"尻尾","answer":["しっぽ"],"meaning":"tail (animal)"},
    {"question":"居候","answer":["いそうろう"],"meaning":"lodger who pays nothing for room and board; freeloader; sponger"},
    {"question":"崖","answer":["がけ"],"meaning":"cliff"},
    {"question":"左利き","answer":["ひだりきき"],"meaning":"left-handedness; left-hander, drinker; wine lover"},
    {"question":"左程","answer":["さほど"],"meaning":"not so; not particularly; not very; not that much"},
    {"question":"差し支える","answer":["さしつかえる"],"meaning":"to interfere; to hinder; to become impeded"},
    {"question":"布巾","answer":["ふきん"],"meaning":"tea-towel; dish cloth"},
    {"question":"幕","answer":["まく"],"meaning":"curtain; bunting, act (in play)"},
    {"question":"年頃","answer":["としごろ"],"meaning":"approximate age; apparent age, marriageable age (esp. of a woman); age of maturity; age of adulthood, appropriate age (to ...); old enough (to ...), past few years; for some years"},
    {"question":"幾多","answer":["いくた"],"meaning":"many; numerous"},
    {"question":"度々","answer":["たびたび"],"meaning":"often; again and again; over and over again; repeatedly; frequently"}
  ]
}
